<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Budget Bytes on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</title>
    <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/author/budget-bytes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Budget Bytes on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2020 07:24:08 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bstreete.github.io/public/author/budget-bytes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Spinach Artichoke Pasta</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/spinach-artichoke-pasta/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2020 07:24:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/spinach-artichoke-pasta/</guid>
      <description>Note: Make a double batch.
Ingredients  2 Tbsp butter 2 cloves garlic 1.5 cups chicken broth 1.5 cups milk 1/4 tsp salt Freshly cracked black pepper 8 oz. linguine 1/4 lb. fresh baby spinach (1/2 of 8oz bag) 1 15oz. can quartered artichoke hearts 1/4 cup grated Parmesan  Directions  Mince the garlic and add it to a deep skillet with the butter. Sauté the garlic in the butter over medium heat for one to two minutes, or just until it&#39;s tender and fragrant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hearty Black Bean Quesadillas</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/black-bean-quesadillas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 15:38:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/black-bean-quesadillas/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 15 oz. can black beans 1 cup frozen corn kernels 1/2 small red onion 1 clove garlic 1/4 bunch fresh cilantro 2 cups shredded cheese 1 batch taco seasoning 10 taco sized tortillas  Directions  Drain the can of beans and rinse lightly. Place the beans in a large bowl along with the corn (no need to thaw). Rinse the cilantro, remove the leaves, and chop roughly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skillet Cornbread</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/cornbread/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 15:31:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/cornbread/</guid>
      <description>Notes This is a modified version of the original recipe. The chili recipe associated with the cornbread was omitted as I prefer a different chili recipe. The cornbread is quite tasty, but can be cooked independently.
Cornbread goes great with honey and/or butter.
Ingredients  1 cup yellow cornmeal 1 cup all-purpose flour 1/4 cup sugar 4 tsp baking powder 1/2 tsp salt 1 cup milk 1 large egg 1/4 cup cooking oil  Directions Instructions</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hoisin Stir Fry Bowls with Spicy Peanut Sauce</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/hoisin-stir-fry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 15:16:36 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/hoisin-stir-fry/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients Can substitute the peanut sauce with crushed peanuts and some sriracha to save time.
Peanut Sauce  1/4 cup natural-style peanut butter 1 Tbsp sriracha 1 tsp soy sauce 1 tsp grated fresh ginger 1 tsp brown sugar 3 Tbsp hot water  Pork and Vegetable Mix  1/2 Tbsp neutral cooking oil 2 cloves garlic 1 tsp grated fresh ginger 1/2 lb ground pork, chicken or turkey 8 oz button mushrooms 1 large carrot 1 red bell pepper 1/3 cup hoisin sauce 1 Tbsp soy sauce 1 tsp toasted sesame oil  Bowl Ingredients  4 cups cooked rice $0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pastalaya</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/pastalaya/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 14:57:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/pastalaya/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 Tbsp vegetable oil 1/2 lb smoked sausage (preferably Andouille) 2 cloves garlic 1 onion 1 bell pepper 2 ribs of celery 15 oz can diced tomatoes 1/2 Tbsp Creole seasoning 1/2 tsp oregano 1/2 tsp smoked paprika 1/4 tsp thyme Freshly cracked pepper 2 cups chicken broth 1 cup water 1 lb penne pasta 2 Tbsp half and half or cream 1/2 bunch fresh parsley 1/2 bunch green onions  Directions  Slice the smoked sausage into thin rounds, then cut any larger pieces in half.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slow Cooker Black Bean Soup</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/black-bean-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 14:51:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/black-bean-soup/</guid>
      <description>Notes Recommend topping with some combination of the following:
 sliced avocado tortilla chips sour cream Tony&#39;s Cajun seasoning  Ingredients  2 cloves garlic 1 medium onion 2 stalks celery 2 medium carrots 1 lb dry uncooked black beans 1 cup salsa 1 Tbsp chili powder 1/2 Tbsp cumin 1 tsp oregano 4 cups vegetable broth 2 cups water  Directions  Mince the garlic, dice the onion and celery, and grate the carrots on a large holed cheese grater.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Broccoli Cheddar Casserole</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/broccoli-cheddar-casserole/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 14:45:39 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/broccoli-cheddar-casserole/</guid>
      <description>Notes You can omit the cayenne if sensitive to heat.
Ingredients  1 lb. frozen broccoli florets 8 oz. medium or sharp cheddar, shredded 4 cups cooked rice (white or brown) 1 small yellow onion 2 cloves garlic 3 Tbsp butter 3 Tbsp all-purpose flour 2 cups milk (2% milk fat or higher) 1/2 tsp salt 1/4 tsp smoked paprika 1/8 tsp cayenne pepper Freshly cracked black pepper  Directions  Roughly chop the broccoli florets into smaller, bite-sized pieces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Not) Butter Chicken</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/not-butter-chicken/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 15:04:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/not-butter-chicken/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1.25 lbs. 2 lg chicken breasts 3 Tbsp butter 3 cloves garlic 1 med onion 1 inch fresh ginger 1 Tbsp garam masala 1/4 tsp cayenne pepper 1 15 oz. can tomato sauce 1 15 oz. can diced tomatoes 1/2 cup plain yogurt 1 1/2 cups jasmine or basmati rice 2 1/4 cups water  Directions  Trim the fat from the chicken breasts and cut them into small chunks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lentil &amp; Sausage Stew</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/lentil-sausage-stew/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 14:55:13 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/lentil-sausage-stew/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1/2 lb Italian sausage 1 medium onion 3 medium carrots (1/2 lb) 4 stalks celery (1/2 bunch) 2 cloves garlic 2 cups brown lentils 6 cups chicken broth 1/2 tsp cayenne 1 tsp smoked paprika 1 tsp cumin 1 tsp oregano 10 oz frozen spinach  Directions  Brown the sausage in a large pot over medium heat, breaking it up into pieces as it cooks. While the sausage is cooking, prepare your vegetables: wash, peel and slice the carrots, slice the celery, dice the onion, and mince the garlic.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>