<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>All Recipes on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</title>
    <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/author/all-recipes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in All Recipes on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 07:53:27 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bstreete.github.io/public/author/all-recipes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Boilermaker Tailgate Chili</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/boilermaker-tailgate-chili/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 07:53:27 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/boilermaker-tailgate-chili/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  2 pounds ground beef chuck 1 pound bulk Italian sausage 3 (15 ounce) cans chili beans, drained 1 (15 ounce) can chili beans in spicy sauce 2 (28 ounce) cans diced tomatoes with juice 1 (6 ounce) can tomato paste 1 large yellow onion, chopped 3 stalks celery, chopped 1 green bell pepper, seeded and chopped 1 red bell pepper, seeded and chopped 2 green chile peppers, seeded and chopped 1 tablespoon bacon bits 4 cubes beef bouillon 1/2 cup beer 1/4 cup chili powder 1 tablespoon Worcestershire sauce 1 tablespoon minced garlic 1 tablespoon dried oregano 2 teaspoons ground cumin 2 teaspoons hot pepper sauce (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Applesauce Cake VI</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/applesauce-cake/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 15:13:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/applesauce-cake/</guid>
      <description>Notes Can substitute green chile applesauce for the regular applesauce for a delicious New Mexican style dessert.
Ingredients  3 cups all-purpose flour 3 teaspoons baking powder 2 teaspoons baking soda 1/2 teaspoon salt 2 teaspoons ground cinnamon 4 eggs 2 cups white sugar 1 1/2 cups vegetable oil 2 cups applesauce 1 teaspoon vanilla extract  Directions  Preheat oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C). Grease and flour a 10 inch tube pan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Authentic Louisiana Red Beans and Rice</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/red-beans-rice/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 17:17:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/red-beans-rice/</guid>
      <description>Note: Can cook in a slow cooker with two cans of prepared kidney beans for four to six hours on low.
Ingredients  1 pound dry kidney beans 1/4 cup olive oil 1 large onion, chopped 1 green bell pepper, chopped 2 tablespoons minced garlic 2 stalks celery, chopped 6 cups water 2 bay leaves 1/2 teaspoon cayenne pepper 1 teaspoon dried thyme 1/4 teaspoon dried sage 1 tablespoon dried parsley 1 teaspoon Cajun seasoning 1 pound andouille sausage, sliced 4 cups water 2 cups long grain white rice  Directions  Rinse beans, and then soak in a large pot of water overnight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Serbian Ground Beef, Veggie, and Potato Bake</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/serbian-beef-potato-bake/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 14:50:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/serbian-beef-potato-bake/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 pound ground beef 1 tablespoon olive oil 1 green bell pepper, chopped 1 onion, chopped 1 carrot, shredded 2 celery stalks, chopped 1/2 tablespoon paprika 1/2 teaspoon salt 3/4 teaspoon black pepper 1/4 teaspoon crushed red pepper 1 pinch ground cinnamon 1 pinch ground cloves 1/4 cup water 1/8 cup red wine 1 cube beef bouillon 2 tablespoons half-and-half 2 potatoes, peeled and sliced  Directions  Preheat oven to 400 degrees F (200 degrees C).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Knead Herb Bread</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/no-knead-herb-bread/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:40:54 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/no-knead-herb-bread/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  3 c all purpose flour 1 tsp salt 1 tbsp sugar 1 (2 1/2 tsp) package active dry yeast 1 1/4 c warm water 2 tbsp shortening or softened butter 3 tsp dried sage 1/2 tsp dried rosemary 1/4 tsp dried thyme 1 tsp melted butter  Directions  Combine 2 cups flour, salt, sugar, and yeast in a large bowl. Stir in the water, shortening, sage, rosemary, and thyme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buffalo Sauce</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/buffalo-sauce/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 07:11:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/buffalo-sauce/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  2/3 cup hot pepper sauce (Frank&#39;s RedHot) 1/2 cup cold unsalted butter 1 1/2 tablespoons white vinegar 1/4 teaspoon Worcestershire sauce 1/4 teaspoon cayenne pepper 1/8 teaspoon garlic powder salt to taste  Directions  Combine the hot sauce, butter, vinegar, Worcestershire sauce, cayenne pepper, garlic powder, and salt in a pot and place over medium heat. Bring to a simmer while stirring with a whisk. As soon as the liquid begins to bubble on the sides of the pot, remove from heat, stir with the whisk, and set aside for use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Braised Balsamic Chicken</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/braised-balsamic-chicken/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 07:11:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/braised-balsamic-chicken/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  6 skinless, boneless chicken breast halves ground black pepper 1 tsp garlic salt 2 tbsp olive oil 1 onion, thinly sliced 1/2 c balsamic vinegar 1 (14.5 oz) can diced tomatoes 1 tsp dried basil 1 tsp dried oregano 1 tsp dried rosemary 1/2 tsp dried thyme  Directions  Season chicken breasts with black pepper and garlic salt. Heat olive oil in medium skillet. Brown the onion and seasoned chicken breasts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweet Potato Black Bean Chili</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/sweet-potato-black-bean-chili/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 18:05:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/sweet-potato-black-bean-chili/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  2 lbs sweet potatoes, peeled and cubed 1/2 tsp ground dried chipotle pepper 1/2 tsp salt 2 tbsp olive oil 1 onion, diced 4 cloves garlic, minced 1 red bell pepper, diced 1 jalapeno pepper, sliced 2 tbsp ancho chile powder, or to taste 1 tbsp ground cumin 1/4 tsp dried oregano 1 (28 oz) can diced tomatoes 1 c water, or more as needed 1 tbsp cornmeal 1 tsp salt, or to taste 1 tsp white sugar 1 tsp unsweetened cocoa powder 2 (15 oz) cans black beans, washed and drained 1 pinch cayenne pepper 1/2 c sour cream for garnish (optional) 1/4 c chopped fresh cilantro (optional)  Directions  Preheat oven to 400 degrees.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>