<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>All Recipes on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</title>
    <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/author/all-recipes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in All Recipes on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 14:50:29 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bstreete.github.io/public/author/all-recipes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Serbian Ground Beef, Veggie, and Potato Bake</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/serbian-beef-potato-bake/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 14:50:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/serbian-beef-potato-bake/</guid>
      <description>Source: All Recipes by amanda1432
Ingredients  1 pound ground beef 1 tablespoon olive oil 1 green bell pepper, chopped 1 onion, chopped 1 carrot, shredded 2 celery stalks, chopped 1/2 tablespoon paprika 1/2 teaspoon salt 3/4 teaspoon black pepper 1/4 teaspoon crushed red pepper 1 pinch ground cinnamon 1 pinch ground cloves 1/4 cup water 1/8 cup red wine 1 cube beef bouillon 2 tablespoons half-and-half 2 potatoes, peeled and sliced  Directions  Preheat oven to 400 degrees F (200 degrees C).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Knead Herb Bread</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/no-knead-herb-bread/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:40:54 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/no-knead-herb-bread/</guid>
      <description>Source: All Recipes
Ingredients  3 c all purpose flour 1 tsp salt 1 tbsp sugar 1 (2 1/2 tsp) package active dry yeast 1 1/4 c warm water 2 tbsp shortening or softened butter 3 tsp dried sage 1/2 tsp dried rosemary 1/4 tsp dried thyme 1 tsp melted butter  Directions  Combine 2 cups flour, salt, sugar, and yeast in a large bowl. Stir in the water, shortening, sage, rosemary, and thyme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buffalo Sauce</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/buffalo-sauce/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 07:11:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/buffalo-sauce/</guid>
      <description>Source: AllRecipes by Chef John
Ingredients  2/3 cup hot pepper sauce (Frank&#39;s RedHot) 1/2 cup cold unsalted butter 1 1/2 tablespoons white vinegar 1/4 teaspoon Worcestershire sauce 1/4 teaspoon cayenne pepper 1/8 teaspoon garlic powder salt to taste  Directions  Combine the hot sauce, butter, vinegar, Worcestershire sauce, cayenne pepper, garlic powder, and salt in a pot and place over medium heat. Bring to a simmer while stirring with a whisk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Braised Balsamic Chicken</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/braised-balsamic-chicken/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 07:11:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/braised-balsamic-chicken/</guid>
      <description>Source: All Recipes by MoonAndBack
Ingredients  6 skinless, boneless chicken breast halves ground black pepper 1 tsp garlic salt 2 tbsp olive oil 1 onion, thinly sliced 1/2 c balsamic vinegar 1 (14.5 oz) can diced tomatoes 1 tsp dried basil 1 tsp dried oregano 1 tsp dried rosemary 1/2 tsp dried thyme  Directions  Season chicken breasts with black pepper and garlic salt. Heat olive oil in medium skillet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweet Potato Black Bean Chili</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/sweet-potato-black-bean-chili/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 18:05:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/sweet-potato-black-bean-chili/</guid>
      <description>Source: AllRecipes by Chef John
Ingredients  2 lbs sweet potatoes, peeled and cubed 1/2 tsp ground dried chipotle pepper 1/2 tsp salt 2 tbsp olive oil 1 onion, diced 4 cloves garlic, minced 1 red bell pepper, diced 1 jalapeno pepper, sliced 2 tbsp ancho chile powder, or to taste 1 tbsp ground cumin 1/4 tsp dried oregano 1 (28 oz) can diced tomatoes 1 c water, or more as needed 1 tbsp cornmeal 1 tsp salt, or to taste 1 tsp white sugar 1 tsp unsweetened cocoa powder 2 (15 oz) cans black beans, washed and drained 1 pinch cayenne pepper 1/2 c sour cream for garnish (optional) 1/4 c chopped fresh cilantro (optional)  Directions  Preheat oven to 400 degrees.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>