<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>pasta on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</title>
    <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/tags/pasta/</link>
    <description>Recent content in pasta on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 15:06:13 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bstreete.github.io/public/tags/pasta/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Pasta With Lemon Cream and Capers</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/lemon-cream-caper-pasta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 15:06:13 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/lemon-cream-caper-pasta/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 pound pasta (penne recommended) 2 tablespoons butter 1 tablespoon all-purpose flour 1 cup heavy cream 3 tablespoons fresh lemon juice 1 tablespoon chicken base (see note) 1 1/2 teaspoons grated lemon zest 1/4 teaspoon kosher salt 1/8 teaspoon ground black pepper 2 tablespoons capers  Directions  For the pasta: In a pot, bring 6 cups water and 1 tablespoon salt to a full boil. Add pasta and cook for about 10 minutes, until al dente.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pastalaya</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/pastalaya/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 14:57:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/pastalaya/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 Tbsp vegetable oil 1/2 lb smoked sausage (preferably Andouille) 2 cloves garlic 1 onion 1 bell pepper 2 ribs of celery 15 oz can diced tomatoes 1/2 Tbsp Creole seasoning 1/2 tsp oregano 1/2 tsp smoked paprika 1/4 tsp thyme Freshly cracked pepper 2 cups chicken broth 1 cup water 1 lb penne pasta 2 Tbsp half and half or cream 1/2 bunch fresh parsley 1/2 bunch green onions  Directions  Slice the smoked sausage into thin rounds, then cut any larger pieces in half.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pasta With Sausage, Squash and Sage Brown Butter </title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/squash-brown-butter-pasta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 14:42:06 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/squash-brown-butter-pasta/</guid>
      <description>Note You can omit the sausage, and the end result is still tasty. You may need to add additional fat to compensate.
Ingredients  1 pound cupped or tubed pasta, like orecchiette or penne 1 pound hot Italian sausage links 2 tablespoons extra-virgin olive oil, plus more for the pasta ¾ pound peeled butternut squash, cut into 1/2-inch cubes (about 2 cups) Salt and pepper 6 tablespoons unsalted butter 8 sage leaves ½ cup grated Parmesan, plus more for garnish  Directions  Bring a large pot of heavily salted water to a boil.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>