<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>pasta on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</title>
    <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/tags/pasta/</link>
    <description>Recent content in pasta on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 08:59:26 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bstreete.github.io/public/tags/pasta/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>White Lasagna</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/white-lasagna/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 08:59:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/white-lasagna/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  8oz lasagna noodles 1 pound ground beef 1 cup finely chopped celery 3/4 finely chopped onion 2 teaspoon dried basil 1 teaspoon dried oregano 2 cup shredded gouda 12 oz mozzerella 1 cup shredded cheddar 1/2 teaspoon Italian seasoning 1 cup light cream (half and half) 3 oz cubed cream cheese 1 clove garlic, minced 1/2 cup white wine 1 egg, slightly beaten 12 oz creamy style cottage cheese (1 1/2 cups) salt and pepper to taste  Directions  In a large skillet, cook ground beef, celery, onion, and garlic until meat is browned and veggies are tender.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pappardelle With Corn</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/pappardelle-corn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 08:14:43 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/pappardelle-corn/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  Kosher salt 2 ears corn, shucked 5 tablespoons unsalted butter 3 cups grape tomatoes 2 cloves garlic, minced Freshly ground pepper 1/2 cup white wine 12 ounces pappardelle pasta 1/2 cup low-sodium chicken broth 1 small bunch scallions, thinly sliced 1/2 cup freshly grated parmesan, plus more for topping Torn basil, for topping  Directions  Bring a large pot of salted water to a boil. Add the corn and cook until slightly tender, about 3 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baked Mac n&#39; Cheese</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/mac-cheese-gallaher/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 07:40:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/mac-cheese-gallaher/</guid>
      <description>Variations Can include chopped green chile, jalapenos, or bacon for an interesting spin on the classic.
Ingredients Casserole Ingredients  4 cups hot, cooked elbow macaroni (roughly 1/2 pound uncooked) 2 cups (8 oz) shredded sharp cheddar 1 cup cottage cheese 3/4 cup sour cream 1/2 cup skim milk 2 tablespoons grated onion 1 1/2 teaspoon butter or margarine, melted 1/2 teaspoon salt 1/4 teaspoon pepper 1 large egg, beaten  Topping Ingredients  1/4 cup bread crumbs 1 tablespoon butter or margarine 1/4 teaspoon paprika  Directions  Preheat oven to 350°.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pasta With Lemon Cream and Capers</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/lemon-cream-caper-pasta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 15:06:13 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/lemon-cream-caper-pasta/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 pound pasta (penne recommended) 2 tablespoons butter 1 tablespoon all-purpose flour 1 cup heavy cream 3 tablespoons fresh lemon juice 1 tablespoon chicken base (see note) 1 1/2 teaspoons grated lemon zest 1/4 teaspoon kosher salt 1/8 teaspoon ground black pepper 2 tablespoons capers  Directions  For the pasta: In a pot, bring 6 cups water and 1 tablespoon salt to a full boil. Add pasta and cook for about 10 minutes, until al dente.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pastalaya</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/pastalaya/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 14:57:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/pastalaya/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 Tbsp vegetable oil 1/2 lb smoked sausage (preferably Andouille) 2 cloves garlic 1 onion 1 bell pepper 2 ribs of celery 15 oz can diced tomatoes 1/2 Tbsp Creole seasoning 1/2 tsp oregano 1/2 tsp smoked paprika 1/4 tsp thyme Freshly cracked pepper 2 cups chicken broth 1 cup water 1 lb penne pasta 2 Tbsp half and half or cream 1/2 bunch fresh parsley 1/2 bunch green onions  Directions  Slice the smoked sausage into thin rounds, then cut any larger pieces in half.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pasta With Sausage, Squash and Sage Brown Butter </title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/squash-brown-butter-pasta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 14:42:06 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/squash-brown-butter-pasta/</guid>
      <description>Note You can omit the sausage, and the end result is still tasty. You may need to add additional fat to compensate.
Ingredients  1 pound cupped or tubed pasta, like orecchiette or penne 1 pound hot Italian sausage links 2 tablespoons extra-virgin olive oil, plus more for the pasta ¾ pound peeled butternut squash, cut into 1/2-inch cubes (about 2 cups) Salt and pepper 6 tablespoons unsalted butter 8 sage leaves ½ cup grated Parmesan, plus more for garnish  Directions  Bring a large pot of heavily salted water to a boil.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>