<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>slow cooker on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</title>
    <link>https://bstreete.github.io/tags/slow-cooker/</link>
    <description>Recent content in slow cooker on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:59:01 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bstreete.github.io/tags/slow-cooker/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Meaty Beany Chili</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/meaty-beany-chili/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:59:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/meaty-beany-chili/</guid>
      <description>Source: The PPK
Ingredients  1 tablespoon olive oil 1 yellow onion, diced medium 1 green pepper, seeded, diced medium 6 cloves garlic, minced 2 jalapenos, thinly sliced (seeded, if you want it less - spicy) 3 to 4 tablespoons mild chili powder 1 tablespoon dried mexican oregano 2 teaspoons ground cumin 1 1/2 teaspoons salt Several dashes fresh black pepper 1/8th teaspoon ground cloves 2 cups water (plus extra as needed) - stock is an acceptable substitute 1 cup dried brown lentils 1 28 oz can crushed tomatoes 1 1/2 cups cooked kidney beans, rinsed and drained (15 oz - can) 1 1/2 cups cooked black beans, rinsed and drained (15 oz - can) 1 tablespoon pure maple syrup 2 tablespoons lime juice  Directions  Set your slow cooker to “sear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slow Cooker Chicken Cacciatore </title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/chicken-cacciatore/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:49:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/chicken-cacciatore/</guid>
      <description>Source: Kitchen Concoctions 
Ingredients  4 skinless, boneless chicken breasts, trimmed and sliced 1 tbsp dried italian seasoning 1 tsp sweet paprika 1 tsp salt 1/2 tsp black pepper 1/4 tsp crushed red pepper (Try it once before adding more) 1 tbsp olive oil 1 yellow bell pepper, sliced into strips 1 orange bell pepper, sliced into strips 1 onion, diced 3 cloves garlic, minced 1 (28 oz) jar pasta sauce 1 bay leaf 1/2 lb pasta, cooked according to directions fresh parsley (optional) parmesan cheese (optional)  Directions  Toss the chicken pieces with the italian seasoning, paprika, salt, pepper, red pepper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balsamic Roast Beef</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/balsamic-roast-beef/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 07:01:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/balsamic-roast-beef/</guid>
      <description>Source: AddAPinch.com
Ingredients  3 – 4 lb chuck roast 1 c beef broth 1/2 c balsamic vinegar 1 tbsp Worcestershire sauce 1 tbsp soy sauce 1 tbsp honey 1/2 tsp red pepper flakes 4 cloves minced garlic  Directions  Place beef in slow cooker. Combine other ingredients in a mixing bowl and pour over the beef. Cook on high 4 hours or low for 6 to 8 hours. (Optional) Reduce the drippings in a saucepan to concentrate the flavor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweet Potato Black Bean Chili</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/sweet-potato-black-bean-chili/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 18:05:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/sweet-potato-black-bean-chili/</guid>
      <description>Source: AllRecipes by Chef John
Ingredients  2 lbs sweet potatoes, peeled and cubed 1/2 tsp ground dried chipotle pepper 1/2 tsp salt 2 tbsp olive oil 1 onion, diced 4 cloves garlic, minced 1 red bell pepper, diced 1 jalapeno pepper, sliced 2 tbsp ancho chile powder, or to taste 1 tbsp ground cumin 1/4 tsp dried oregano 1 (28 oz) can diced tomatoes 1 c water, or more as needed 1 tbsp cornmeal 1 tsp salt, or to taste 1 tsp white sugar 1 tsp unsweetened cocoa powder 2 (15 oz) cans black beans, washed and drained 1 pinch cayenne pepper 1/2 c sour cream for garnish (optional) 1/4 c chopped fresh cilantro (optional)  Directions  Preheat oven to 400 degrees.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>