<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kelly Family on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</title>
    <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/author/kelly-family/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Kelly Family on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 07:48:48 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bstreete.github.io/public/author/kelly-family/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Forestier</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/chicken-forestier/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 07:48:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/chicken-forestier/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 pound boneless, skinless chicken breasts 1/4 cup all purpose flour 4 tablespoons butter 1/2 pound mushrooms 1/2 cup dry vermouth 2 tablespoons water 3/4 teaspoon salt dash of pepper 1 tablespoon chopped parsley  Directions  On a cutting board, pound chicken breast to about 1/8 to 1/4 inch thickness. Coat chicken lightly with flour. Melt butter over medium high heat, and cook chicken breasts until light brown on both sides.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chile Relleno Casserole</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/chile-relleno-casserole/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 07:42:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/chile-relleno-casserole/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  12 to 15 green chiles; roasted, seeded, and peeled 4 cups grated cheddar 5 eggs 1 1/4 cup of milk 1/4 cup of flour salt and pepper  Directions  Preheat oven to 350°. Lay chiles flat in bottom of casserole dish sprayed with cooking spray. Sprinkle two cups of cheese over the chiles, then add a second layer of chiles. Mix eggs, milk, flour, salt, and pepper together and pour over chiles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chevre and Herb Mousse</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/chevre-herb-mousse/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 07:38:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/chevre-herb-mousse/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1/2 cup parsley leaves 1/2 teaspoon crushed garlic 1 bunch of tarragon leaves (about 1/4 cup) 1 cup of goat cheese 1 1/2 pounds of cream cheese  Directions  Chop parsley leaves, crushed, garlic, and tarragon leaves in food processor using short pulses until finely minced. Remove from food processor to a small bowl. Blend goat cheese and cream cheese in the food processor until creamy and smooth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Banana Bread</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/banana-bread/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 15:44:57 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/banana-bread/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1/2 cup butter 1 cup sugar 2 beaten eggs 3 ripe, mashed bananas 2 cups all purpose flour 1 teaspoon salt 1 teaspoon baking soda mixed with 3 tablespoons of cold water 1 teaspoon vanilla 1/2 cup chopped nuts  Directions  Cream butter and sugar until light. Add beaten eggs and mashed bananas. Sift flour and salt together and add to the first mixture. Add baking soda, vanilla, and nuts and mix well.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>