<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>vegetarian on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</title>
    <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/tags/vegetarian/</link>
    <description>Recent content in vegetarian on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 14:51:20 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bstreete.github.io/public/tags/vegetarian/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Slow Cooker Black Bean Soup</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/black-bean-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 14:51:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/black-bean-soup/</guid>
      <description>Notes Recommend topping with some combination of the following:
 sliced avocado tortilla chips sour cream Tony&#39;s Cajun seasoning  Ingredients  2 cloves garlic 1 medium onion 2 stalks celery 2 medium carrots 1 lb dry uncooked black beans 1 cup salsa 1 Tbsp chili powder 1/2 Tbsp cumin 1 tsp oregano 4 cups vegetable broth 2 cups water  Directions  Mince the garlic, dice the onion and celery, and grate the carrots on a large holed cheese grater.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Broccoli Cheddar Casserole</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/broccoli-cheddar-casserole/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 14:45:39 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/broccoli-cheddar-casserole/</guid>
      <description>Notes You can omit the cayenne if sensitive to heat.
Ingredients  1 lb. frozen broccoli florets 8 oz. medium or sharp cheddar, shredded 4 cups cooked rice (white or brown) 1 small yellow onion 2 cloves garlic 3 Tbsp butter 3 Tbsp all-purpose flour 2 cups milk (2% milk fat or higher) 1/2 tsp salt 1/4 tsp smoked paprika 1/8 tsp cayenne pepper Freshly cracked black pepper  Directions  Roughly chop the broccoli florets into smaller, bite-sized pieces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homemade Falafel with Tahini Sauce</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/falafel-with-tahini/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 17:14:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/falafel-with-tahini/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients Falafel  2 cups roughly chopped white onion 6 garlic cloves 2 cups cooked chickpeas, drained 1 cup lightly packed parsley leaves 1 cup lightly packed cilantro leaves 1 teaspoon salt 1/4 teaspoon chili powder 2 teaspoons cumin 2 teaspoons baking powder 1/2 cup all-purpose flour Canola oil, for sauteing Pita bread, for serving  Tahini Sauce  1/4 cups plain yogurt (full fat or non-fat) /4 cup tahini (sesame paste) Tablespoons fresh lemon juice  Directions  Add the onion and garlic cloves to the bowl of a food processor and pulse just until they are finely minced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roasted Butternut Squash Soup</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/butternut-squash-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 14:49:43 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/butternut-squash-soup/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 Large (2 to 3 pound) butternut squash 1 tablespoon olive oil salt and pepper to taste 1 onion, roughly chopped 1 tablespoon chopped fresh sage 3 garlic cloves, roasted 4 cups vegetable broth 1/4 cup toasted pumpkin seeds (optional)  Directions  Preheat oven to 400°F. Line or grease a baking sheet. Cut the squash in half lengthwise and remove the seeds. Place on the baking sheet, brush with olive oil, and sprinkle with salt and pepper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kale Salad with Mustard Vinaigrette</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/kale-salad-mustard-vinaigrette/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 14:39:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/kale-salad-mustard-vinaigrette/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients Salad  Medium bunch of kale (best with Lacinto aka &amp;lsquo;Dinosaur&amp;rsquo; kale) 1/2 cup pecan or walnut pieces 1/2 cup dried cherries or cranberries 1/4 cup queso fresco or soft goat cheese 1/2 cup Mustard Vinaigrette  Mustard Vinaigrette Dressing  1/2 small red onion, chopped finely (roughly 1/4 cup) 2 tablespoons rice wine vinegar 1 tablespoon Dijon mustard 1/4 teaspoon salt 1/2 teaspoon pepper 2/3 cup olive oil  Directions Salad  Wash kale and pat dry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meaty Beany Chili</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/meaty-beany-chili/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:59:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/meaty-beany-chili/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 tablespoon olive oil 1 yellow onion, diced medium 1 green pepper, seeded, diced medium 6 cloves garlic, minced 2 jalapenos, thinly sliced (seeded, if you want it less - spicy) 3 to 4 tablespoons mild chili powder 1 tablespoon dried mexican oregano 2 teaspoons ground cumin 1 1/2 teaspoons salt Several dashes fresh black pepper 1/8th teaspoon ground cloves 2 cups water (plus extra as needed) - stock is an acceptable substitute 1 cup dried brown lentils 1 28 oz can crushed tomatoes 1 1/2 cups cooked kidney beans, rinsed and drained (15 oz - can) 1 1/2 cups cooked black beans, rinsed and drained (15 oz - can) 1 tablespoon pure maple syrup 2 tablespoons lime juice  Directions  Set your slow cooker to “sear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pappa Al Pomodoro</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/pappa-al-pomodoro/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:47:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/pappa-al-pomodoro/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  2 lb tomatoes, cored and quartered 2 garlic cloves, smashed 1/2 tsp fennel seeds 6 tbsp olive oil Kosher salt Black pepper 4 sprigs basil 1/4 loaf country style bread, crust removed torn into 2&amp;rdquo; pieces  Directions  Preheat oven to 450. Toss tomatoes, garlic, fennel, and 3 tbsp olive oil in a large baking dish. Season with salt and pepper. Roast, stirring occasionally, until the tomatoes are browned and the juices thicken, 30 to 35 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweet Potato Black Bean Chili</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/sweet-potato-black-bean-chili/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 18:05:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/sweet-potato-black-bean-chili/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  2 lbs sweet potatoes, peeled and cubed 1/2 tsp ground dried chipotle pepper 1/2 tsp salt 2 tbsp olive oil 1 onion, diced 4 cloves garlic, minced 1 red bell pepper, diced 1 jalapeno pepper, sliced 2 tbsp ancho chile powder, or to taste 1 tbsp ground cumin 1/4 tsp dried oregano 1 (28 oz) can diced tomatoes 1 c water, or more as needed 1 tbsp cornmeal 1 tsp salt, or to taste 1 tsp white sugar 1 tsp unsweetened cocoa powder 2 (15 oz) cans black beans, washed and drained 1 pinch cayenne pepper 1/2 c sour cream for garnish (optional) 1/4 c chopped fresh cilantro (optional)  Directions  Preheat oven to 400 degrees.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>