<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>entree on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</title>
    <link>https://bstreete.github.io/tags/entree/</link>
    <description>Recent content in entree on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 10:02:26 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bstreete.github.io/tags/entree/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Crepes</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/crepes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 10:02:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/crepes/</guid>
      <description>Source: Veronica Bower&#39;s French family
Ingredients  1 cup flour 1 cup milk 1/4 cup sugar (for dinner crepes (ex: ham &amp;amp; cheese), decrease sugar by 1/2) 4 eggs 1 tablespoon oil  Directions  Mix flour, milk, sugar, eggs, and oil in bowl. Batter should be runny. Heat medium size nonstick frying pan to medium heat. Spray pan with cooking spray (only on first crepe). Place 1/4 cup batter in pan an switch around until bottom is covered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweet Potato Pancakes</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/sweet-potato-pancakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 10:00:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/sweet-potato-pancakes/</guid>
      <description>Source: The Garden Kitchen
Ingredients  1 pound sweet potatoes (about 2 medium), peeled and coarsely grated 2 scallions, finely chopped 1/3 cup all-purpose flour 2 large eggs, lightly beaten 1 teaspoon salt 1/2 teaspoon black pepper 1/2 teaspoon powdered garlic 1/2 teaspoon ground cumin 2 tablespoons vegetable oil  Directions  Wash hands with soap and warm water. Wash produce well and chop as directed. Stir together all ingredients, except oil, until well mixed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meaty Beany Chili</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/meaty-beany-chili/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:59:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/meaty-beany-chili/</guid>
      <description>Source: The PPK
Ingredients  1 tablespoon olive oil 1 yellow onion, diced medium 1 green pepper, seeded, diced medium 6 cloves garlic, minced 2 jalapenos, thinly sliced (seeded, if you want it less - spicy) 3 to 4 tablespoons mild chili powder 1 tablespoon dried mexican oregano 2 teaspoons ground cumin 1 1/2 teaspoons salt Several dashes fresh black pepper 1/8th teaspoon ground cloves 2 cups water (plus extra as needed) - stock is an acceptable substitute 1 cup dried brown lentils 1 28 oz can crushed tomatoes 1 1/2 cups cooked kidney beans, rinsed and drained (15 oz - can) 1 1/2 cups cooked black beans, rinsed and drained (15 oz - can) 1 tablespoon pure maple syrup 2 tablespoons lime juice  Directions  Set your slow cooker to “sear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Italian Sausage with Potatoes and Peppers </title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/italian-sausage-potatoes-peppers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:58:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/italian-sausage-potatoes-peppers/</guid>
      <description>Source: Robyn Kelly
Ingredients  1 1/2 pounds Italian sausage 3 to 5 Russet potatoes 3 green peppers 1/4 cup water Salt and pepper to taste 1 onion  Directions  Preheat oven to 400°. Slice potatoes thin and layer on bottom of baking dish. Season potatoes. Thinly slice peppers and onions; layer over the potatoes before seasoning. Crumble uncooked sausage over the vegetables. Pour water into baking dish; cover dish with foil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baked French Toast</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/baked-french-toast/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:56:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/baked-french-toast/</guid>
      <description>Source: Lis Handley
Ingredients  Loaf of French bread 3 eggs 3 tablespoons sugar 1 teaspoon vanilla 2 1/4 cup milk 1/2 cup flour 6 tablespoons brown sugar 1/2 teaspoon cinnamon 1/4 cup butter 1 cup berries  Directions  Cut bread diagonally. Place in baking dish. Beat eggs, sugard, and vanilla together. Stir in milk and pour over bread. Turn slices to coat well. Cover and refrigerate at least two hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2am Chili</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/2am-chili/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:53:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/2am-chili/</guid>
      <description>Source: r/pics
Ingredients  2 tablespoons flour 1 teaspoon basil 1 tablespoon onion powder 4 teaspoons chili powder 2 teaspoons cumin 1 tablespoon cayenne 1 tablespoon garlic powder 2 teaspoons sugar 3 to 4 cloves of garlic 1 onion 1 bell pepper 1 1/2 pounds of ground beef 1 15oz can of tomato sauce 1 15oz can of diced tomatoes 1 15oz can of corn 1 15oz can of kidney beans 1 can of beer (optional)  Directions  Brown the beef in a skillet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slow Cooker Chicken Cacciatore </title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/chicken-cacciatore/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:49:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/chicken-cacciatore/</guid>
      <description>Source: Kitchen Concoctions 
Ingredients  4 skinless, boneless chicken breasts, trimmed and sliced 1 tbsp dried italian seasoning 1 tsp sweet paprika 1 tsp salt 1/2 tsp black pepper 1/4 tsp crushed red pepper (Try it once before adding more) 1 tbsp olive oil 1 yellow bell pepper, sliced into strips 1 orange bell pepper, sliced into strips 1 onion, diced 3 cloves garlic, minced 1 (28 oz) jar pasta sauce 1 bay leaf 1/2 lb pasta, cooked according to directions fresh parsley (optional) parmesan cheese (optional)  Directions  Toss the chicken pieces with the italian seasoning, paprika, salt, pepper, red pepper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pappa Al Pomodoro</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/pappa-al-pomodoro/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:47:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/pappa-al-pomodoro/</guid>
      <description>Source: Bon Appetit August 2014
Ingredients  2 lb tomatoes, cored and quartered 2 garlic cloves, smashed 1/2 tsp fennel seeds 6 tbsp olive oil Kosher salt Black pepper 4 sprigs basil 1/4 loaf country style bread, crust removed torn into 2&amp;rdquo; pieces  Directions  Preheat oven to 450. Toss tomatoes, garlic, fennel, and 3 tbsp olive oil in a large baking dish. Season with salt and pepper. Roast, stirring occasionally, until the tomatoes are browned and the juices thicken, 30 to 35 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manga Kalan (Keralan Mango Curry) </title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/manga-kalan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:39:27 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/manga-kalan/</guid>
      <description>Source: Saveur Issue 162
Ingredients  2 3/4 c freshly grated or desiccated coconut 1/2 tbsp cumin seeds 4 small Thai green chiles or 2 serrano chiles, chopped 5 medium green mangoes, peeled and sliced 1 tbsp grated jaggery or light brown sugar 1 tsp cayenne 1 tsp ground turmeric Kosher salt to taste 1 1/4 c whole fat yogurt 2 tbsp coconut or canola oil 1/4 tsp brown mustard seeds 1/4 tsp fenugreek seeds 12 fresh or frozen curry leaves 3 dried chiles de arbol, stemmed and halved  Directions  Puree coconut, cumin, chiles, and 1 c water in a food processor until smooth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kill City Chili</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/kill-city-chili/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:37:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/kill-city-chili/</guid>
      <description>Source: Saveur Issue 162 
Ingredients  3 tbsp olive oil 2 1/2 lbs ground beef 1/4 c dark chile powder 2 1/2 tbsp curry powder 3 cloves garlic, finely chopped 1 large yellow onion, diced 1 medium green bell pepper, diced 2 16 oz cans kideny beans, drained and rinsed 1 28 oz can crushed tomatoes Kosher salt and ground black pepper, to taste 3 tbsp chopped cilantro, plus more for garnish 1 c grated Monterey Jack cheese for serving Sour cream for serving  Directions  Heat oil in a 6 qt saucepan over medium high heat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feta Walnut Pasta</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/feta-walnut-pasta/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:26:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/feta-walnut-pasta/</guid>
      <description>Source: Athenos and Colavita Ad
Ingredients  8 oz rotelle or fusilli pasta 1/2 c chopped walnuts 1 clove garlic, minced 1/2 c sliced green onions 1/3 c extra virgin olive oil 8 oz feta cheese, crumbled 5 oz sliced olives, drained 1/4 c chopped fresh basil  Directions  Cook pasta, and drain. Toast walnuts in a large non-stick skillet on medium high heat 5 minutes, stirring constantly. Remove walnuts from skillet, set aside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chile Verde</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/chile-verde/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:08:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/chile-verde/</guid>
      <description>Source: Simply Recipes
Ingredients  1 1/2 pounds tomatillos 5 garlic cloves, not peeled 2 jalapenos, seeds and ribs removed, chopped 2 Anaheim or Poblano chiles (optional) 1 bunch cilantro leaves, cleaned and chopped 3 1/2 to 4 pounds pork shoulder (also called pork butt), trimmed of - excess fat and cut into 1 to 2-inch cubes Salt Freshly ground black pepper Olive oil 2 yellow onions, chopped 3 garlic cloves, peeled and finely chopped 2 Tbsp of chopped fresh oregano or 1 Tbsp of dried oregano 2 1/2 cups chicken stock Pinch of ground cloves  Directions  Remove papery husks from tomatillos and rinse well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Melting Pot Cheddar Cheese Fondue</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/cheddar-fondue/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 08:48:41 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/cheddar-fondue/</guid>
      <description>Source: CopyKat Recipes
Ingredients  6 oz medium sharp cheddar cheese 2 oz Emmenthaler Swiss cheese 4 oz Coors Light 2 tsp chopped garlic 2 tsp Worcestershire sauce 2 Tbsp flour 2 tsp dry mustard powder  Directions  If you are using a fondue pot, turn it onto medium heat Otherwise, use a double boiler to heat the mixture. Combine beer, garlic, mustard powder, and Worcestershire sauce. Shred or cube all cheese, and toss with flour coating the cheese well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buffalo Sauce</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/buffalo-sauce/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 07:11:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/buffalo-sauce/</guid>
      <description>Source: AllRecipes by Chef John
Ingredients  2/3 cup hot pepper sauce (Frank&#39;s RedHot) 1/2 cup cold unsalted butter 1 1/2 tablespoons white vinegar 1/4 teaspoon Worcestershire sauce 1/4 teaspoon cayenne pepper 1/8 teaspoon garlic powder salt to taste  Directions  Combine the hot sauce, butter, vinegar, Worcestershire sauce, cayenne pepper, garlic powder, and salt in a pot and place over medium heat. Bring to a simmer while stirring with a whisk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Braised Balsamic Chicken</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/braised-balsamic-chicken/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 07:11:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/braised-balsamic-chicken/</guid>
      <description>Source: All Recipes by MoonAndBack
Ingredients  6 skinless, boneless chicken breast halves ground black pepper 1 tsp garlic salt 2 tbsp olive oil 1 onion, thinly sliced 1/2 c balsamic vinegar 1 (14.5 oz) can diced tomatoes 1 tsp dried basil 1 tsp dried oregano 1 tsp dried rosemary 1/2 tsp dried thyme  Directions  Season chicken breasts with black pepper and garlic salt. Heat olive oil in medium skillet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balsamic Roast Beef</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/balsamic-roast-beef/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 07:01:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/balsamic-roast-beef/</guid>
      <description>Source: AddAPinch.com
Ingredients  3 – 4 lb chuck roast 1 c beef broth 1/2 c balsamic vinegar 1 tbsp Worcestershire sauce 1 tbsp soy sauce 1 tbsp honey 1/2 tsp red pepper flakes 4 cloves minced garlic  Directions  Place beef in slow cooker. Combine other ingredients in a mixing bowl and pour over the beef. Cook on high 4 hours or low for 6 to 8 hours. (Optional) Reduce the drippings in a saucepan to concentrate the flavor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweet Potato Black Bean Chili</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/sweet-potato-black-bean-chili/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 18:05:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/sweet-potato-black-bean-chili/</guid>
      <description>Source: AllRecipes by Chef John
Ingredients  2 lbs sweet potatoes, peeled and cubed 1/2 tsp ground dried chipotle pepper 1/2 tsp salt 2 tbsp olive oil 1 onion, diced 4 cloves garlic, minced 1 red bell pepper, diced 1 jalapeno pepper, sliced 2 tbsp ancho chile powder, or to taste 1 tbsp ground cumin 1/4 tsp dried oregano 1 (28 oz) can diced tomatoes 1 c water, or more as needed 1 tbsp cornmeal 1 tsp salt, or to taste 1 tsp white sugar 1 tsp unsweetened cocoa powder 2 (15 oz) cans black beans, washed and drained 1 pinch cayenne pepper 1/2 c sour cream for garnish (optional) 1/4 c chopped fresh cilantro (optional)  Directions  Preheat oven to 400 degrees.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>