<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>entree on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</title>
    <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/tags/entree/</link>
    <description>Recent content in entree on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 14:45:39 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bstreete.github.io/public/tags/entree/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Broccoli Cheddar Casserole</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/broccoli-cheddar-casserole/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 14:45:39 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/broccoli-cheddar-casserole/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 lb. frozen broccoli florets 8 oz. medium or sharp cheddar, shredded 4 cups cooked rice (white or brown) 1 small yellow onion 2 cloves garlic 3 Tbsp butter 3 Tbsp all-purpose flour 2 cups milk (2% milk fat or higher) 1/2 tsp salt 1/4 tsp smoked paprika 1/8 tsp cayenne pepper Freshly cracked black pepper  Directions  Roughly chop the broccoli florets into smaller, bite-sized pieces. Combine the broccoli, about 3/4 of the shredded cheddar, and the pre-cooked rice in a large bowl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pasta With Sausage, Squash and Sage Brown Butter </title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/squash-brown-butter-pasta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 14:42:06 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/squash-brown-butter-pasta/</guid>
      <description>Note You can omit the sausage, and the end result is still tasty. You may need to add additional fat to compensate.
Ingredients  1 pound cupped or tubed pasta, like orecchiette or penne 1 pound hot Italian sausage links 2 tablespoons extra-virgin olive oil, plus more for the pasta ¾ pound peeled butternut squash, cut into 1/2-inch cubes (about 2 cups) Salt and pepper 6 tablespoons unsalted butter 8 sage leaves ½ cup grated Parmesan, plus more for garnish  Directions  Bring a large pot of heavily salted water to a boil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slow Cooker Pot Roast</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/slow-cook-pot-roast/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 07:11:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/slow-cook-pot-roast/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  One 4-pound beef chuck roast Kosher salt and freshly ground black pepper 1/3 cup all-purpose flour, plus more for coating 3 tablespoons olive oil 4 medium carrots, cut into 2-inch pieces 3 stalks celery, peeled and cut into 2-inch pieces 1 medium onion, cut into 1/2-inch wedges 3 cloves garlic, mashed 3 tablespoons tomato paste 1 cup red wine 3 cups low-sodium beef broth 3 bay leaves 2 sprigs fresh thyme 1/2 teaspoon ground allspice 1/2 cup loosely packed parsley leaves, chopped  Directions  Sprinkle the roast all over with 2 1/2 teaspoons salt and 1 1/2 teaspoons pepper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buddha Bowls</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/buddha-bowls/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 07:07:58 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/buddha-bowls/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 large sweet potato, peeled and cut into 1/2-inch cubes 1 large red onion, diced 3 tbsp. extra-virgin olive oil, divided Kosher salt Freshly ground black pepper 1 lb. boneless, skinless chicken breasts 1/2 tsp. garlic powder 1/2 tsp. ground ginger 1 small clove garlic, minced 2 tbsp. creamy peanut butter 1/4 c. Juice of 1 lime 1 tbsp. low-sodium soy sauce 1 tbsp. honey 1 tbsp. toasted sesame oil 4 c.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cross Rib Roast</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/rib-roast/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2019 12:31:07 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/rib-roast/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  2 pounds cross-rib roast 2 tablespoons balsamic vinegar 2 tablespoons minced garlic 2 teaspoons dried thyme 1 teaspoon dried rosemary 1 tablespoon salt 1 teaspoon pepper 1 tablespoon olive oil  Directions  Brush roast with balsamic vinegar. Make a paste with remaining ingredients and apply to meat. Roast meat at 450 for 15 minutes. Reduce heat to 350 and cook for 40 to 60 minutes, or until internal temperature reaches 125.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Authentic Louisiana Red Beans and Rice</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/red-beans-rice/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 17:17:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/red-beans-rice/</guid>
      <description>Note: Can cook in a slow cooker with two cans of prepared kidney beans for four to six hours on low.
Ingredients  1 pound dry kidney beans 1/4 cup olive oil 1 large onion, chopped 1 green bell pepper, chopped 2 tablespoons minced garlic 2 stalks celery, chopped 6 cups water 2 bay leaves 1/2 teaspoon cayenne pepper 1 teaspoon dried thyme 1/4 teaspoon dried sage 1 tablespoon dried parsley 1 teaspoon Cajun seasoning 1 pound andouille sausage, sliced 4 cups water 2 cups long grain white rice  Directions  Rinse beans, and then soak in a large pot of water overnight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homemade Falafel with Tahini Sauce</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/falafel-with-tahini/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 17:14:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/falafel-with-tahini/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients Falafel  2 cups roughly chopped white onion 6 garlic cloves 2 cups cooked chickpeas, drained 1 cup lightly packed parsley leaves 1 cup lightly packed cilantro leaves 1 teaspoon salt 1/4 teaspoon chili powder 2 teaspoons cumin 2 teaspoons baking powder 1/2 cup all-purpose flour Canola oil, for sauteing Pita bread, for serving  Tahini Sauce  1/4 cups plain yogurt (full fat or non-fat) /4 cup tahini (sesame paste) Tablespoons fresh lemon juice  Directions  Add the onion and garlic cloves to the bowl of a food processor and pulse just until they are finely minced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Potatoes, Peppers, and Kielbasa Skillet</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/kielbasa-potatoes-peppers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 17:09:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/kielbasa-potatoes-peppers/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  3 Tablespoons olive oil 3 potatoes chopped 2 sweet bell peppers chopped 1 onion chopped 14 oz kielbasa sliced 1/2 teaspoon salt 1/4 teaspoon pepper 1/4 teaspoon oregano 1/4 basil 1 teaspoon crushed garlic  Directions  Preheat oven to 375 degrees. Using 1 Tablespoon of olive oil, spread all over a cast iron or oven proof skillet. In a large bowl add your vegetables and kielbasa. Pour the rest of the olive oil over along with the spices and mix well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Not) Butter Chicken</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/not-butter-chicken/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 15:04:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/not-butter-chicken/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1.25 lbs. 2 lg chicken breasts 3 Tbsp butter 3 cloves garlic 1 med onion 1 inch fresh ginger 1 Tbsp garam masala 1/4 tsp cayenne pepper 1 15 oz. can tomato sauce 1 15 oz. can diced tomatoes 1/2 cup plain yogurt 1 1/2 cups jasmine or basmati rice 2 1/4 cups water  Directions  Trim the fat from the chicken breasts and cut them into small chunks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>La Taqueria Carnitas</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/carnitas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 15:02:36 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/carnitas/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 boned, tied pork shoulder or butt (4 to 5 lb.) 2 onions (1 lb. total), peeled and quartered 4 stalks celery (including leaves), rinsed and cut into chunks 4 cloves garlic, peeled 2 dried bay leaves 2 teaspoons dried thyme About 1 teaspoon salt 1/2 cup milk  Directions  Rinse pork and put in a 6- to 8-quart pan. Add onions, celery, garlic, bay leaves, thyme, 1 teaspoon salt, and enough water to cover meat&amp;ndash;2 1/2 to 3 1/2 quarts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Instant Pot Mac and Cheese</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/instant-pot-mac-and-cheese/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 15:00:34 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/instant-pot-mac-and-cheese/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 lb Elbow Noodles 1 Cup Guinness Beer 3 Cups Water 2 Tablespoons Butter 1 Tablespoon Dry Mustard Powder 2 Ounces Cream Cheese cut into cubes 1 Can Eveporated Milk 1/2 Teaspoon Salt 1/2 Teaspoon Pepper or to taste 14 Ounces Kerrygold Irish Cheddar 2 bricks 1 Cup Monterey Jack Cheese  Directions  Add beer, water, noodles, butter, mustard powder, salt and pepper to Instant Pot. Cover and cook on manual pressure for 3 minutes When timer is done preform a quick release.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Better than Takeout Ham Fried Rice</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/ham-fried-rice/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 14:58:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/ham-fried-rice/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1½ cups- 2 cups chopped ham 3 cups cooked rice 2 Tbs sesame oil 1 small white onion, chopped 1 cup frozen peas and carrots, thawed 2-3 Tablespoons soy sauce (more or less to taste) 3 eggs, lightly beaten 2 Tbsp chopped green onions (optional)  Directions  Preheat a large skillet or wok to medium heat. Pour sesame oil in the bottom. Add white onion, chopped ham, peas and carrots and fry until tender.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lentil &amp; Sausage Stew</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/lentil-sausage-stew/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 14:55:13 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/lentil-sausage-stew/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1/2 lb Italian sausage 1 medium onion 3 medium carrots (1/2 lb) 4 stalks celery (1/2 bunch) 2 cloves garlic 2 cups brown lentils 6 cups chicken broth 1/2 tsp cayenne 1 tsp smoked paprika 1 tsp cumin 1 tsp oregano 10 oz frozen spinach  Directions  Brown the sausage in a large pot over medium heat, breaking it up into pieces as it cooks. While the sausage is cooking, prepare your vegetables: wash, peel and slice the carrots, slice the celery, dice the onion, and mince the garlic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Potato Soup with Bacon and Cheddar</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/potato-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 14:52:05 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/potato-soup/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  4 strips bacon, diced 2 cups chopped yellow onion 1/4 cup minced shallot 1 tablespoon minced garlic 2 1/2 pounds Idaho potatoes, peeled and cut into 1/2-inch dice, reserved in a bowl of cold water 5 cups chicken stock or canned, low-sodium chicken broth 3/4 teaspoon salt 1/4 teaspoon ground white pepper 1/4 teaspoon ground black pepper, plus more for garnish 1/2 cup heavy cream 2 tablespoons chopped green onion tops, plus more for garnish 8 ounces grated sharp Cheddar, for garnish (recommend doubling)  Note: Can use broccoli instead of bacon, and olive oil instead of bacon grease for a lighter soup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Serbian Ground Beef, Veggie, and Potato Bake</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/serbian-beef-potato-bake/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 14:50:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/serbian-beef-potato-bake/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 pound ground beef 1 tablespoon olive oil 1 green bell pepper, chopped 1 onion, chopped 1 carrot, shredded 2 celery stalks, chopped 1/2 tablespoon paprika 1/2 teaspoon salt 3/4 teaspoon black pepper 1/4 teaspoon crushed red pepper 1 pinch ground cinnamon 1 pinch ground cloves 1/4 cup water 1/8 cup red wine 1 cube beef bouillon 2 tablespoons half-and-half 2 potatoes, peeled and sliced  Directions  Preheat oven to 400 degrees F (200 degrees C).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roasted Butternut Squash Soup</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/butternut-squash-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 14:49:43 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/butternut-squash-soup/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 Large (2 to 3 pound) butternut squash 1 tablespoon olive oil salt and pepper to taste 1 onion, roughly chopped 1 tablespoon chopped fresh sage 3 garlic cloves, roasted 4 cups vegetable broth 1/4 cup toasted pumpkin seeds (optional)  Directions  Preheat oven to 400°F. Line or grease a baking sheet. Cut the squash in half lengthwise and remove the seeds. Place on the baking sheet, brush with olive oil, and sprinkle with salt and pepper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crepes</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/crepes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 10:02:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/crepes/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 cup flour 1 cup milk 1/4 cup sugar (for dinner crepes (ex: ham &amp;amp; cheese), decrease sugar by 1/2) 4 eggs 1 tablespoon oil  Directions  Mix flour, milk, sugar, eggs, and oil in bowl. Batter should be runny. Heat medium size nonstick frying pan to medium heat. Spray pan with cooking spray (only on first crepe). Place 1/4 cup batter in pan an switch around until bottom is covered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweet Potato Pancakes</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/sweet-potato-pancakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 10:00:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/sweet-potato-pancakes/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 pound sweet potatoes (about 2 medium), peeled and coarsely grated 2 scallions, finely chopped 1/3 cup all-purpose flour 2 large eggs, lightly beaten 1 teaspoon salt 1/2 teaspoon black pepper 1/2 teaspoon powdered garlic 1/2 teaspoon ground cumin 2 tablespoons vegetable oil  Directions  Wash hands with soap and warm water. Wash produce well and chop as directed. Stir together all ingredients, except oil, until well mixed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meaty Beany Chili</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/meaty-beany-chili/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:59:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/meaty-beany-chili/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 tablespoon olive oil 1 yellow onion, diced medium 1 green pepper, seeded, diced medium 6 cloves garlic, minced 2 jalapenos, thinly sliced (seeded, if you want it less - spicy) 3 to 4 tablespoons mild chili powder 1 tablespoon dried mexican oregano 2 teaspoons ground cumin 1 1/2 teaspoons salt Several dashes fresh black pepper 1/8th teaspoon ground cloves 2 cups water (plus extra as needed) - stock is an acceptable substitute 1 cup dried brown lentils 1 28 oz can crushed tomatoes 1 1/2 cups cooked kidney beans, rinsed and drained (15 oz - can) 1 1/2 cups cooked black beans, rinsed and drained (15 oz - can) 1 tablespoon pure maple syrup 2 tablespoons lime juice  Directions  Set your slow cooker to “sear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Italian Sausage with Potatoes and Peppers </title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/italian-sausage-potatoes-peppers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:58:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/italian-sausage-potatoes-peppers/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 1/2 pounds Italian sausage 3 to 5 Russet potatoes 3 green peppers 1/4 cup water Salt and pepper to taste 1 onion  Directions  Preheat oven to 400°. Slice potatoes thin and layer on bottom of baking dish. Season potatoes. Thinly slice peppers and onions; layer over the potatoes before seasoning. Crumble uncooked sausage over the vegetables. Pour water into baking dish; cover dish with foil. Bake 1 1/2 hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baked French Toast</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/baked-french-toast/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:56:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/baked-french-toast/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  Loaf of French bread 3 eggs 3 tablespoons sugar 1 teaspoon vanilla 2 1/4 cup milk 1/2 cup flour 6 tablespoons brown sugar 1/2 teaspoon cinnamon 1/4 cup butter 1 cup berries  Directions  Cut bread diagonally. Place in baking dish. Beat eggs, sugard, and vanilla together. Stir in milk and pour over bread. Turn slices to coat well. Cover and refrigerate at least two hours. Preheat oven to 375°.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2am Chili</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/2am-chili/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:53:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/2am-chili/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  2 tablespoons flour 1 teaspoon basil 1 tablespoon onion powder 4 teaspoons chili powder 2 teaspoons cumin 1 tablespoon cayenne 1 tablespoon garlic powder 2 teaspoons sugar 3 to 4 cloves of garlic 1 onion 1 bell pepper 1 1/2 pounds of ground beef 1 15oz can of tomato sauce 1 15oz can of diced tomatoes 1 15oz can of corn 1 15oz can of kidney beans 1 can of beer (optional)  Directions  Brown the beef in a skillet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slow Cooker Chicken Cacciatore </title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/chicken-cacciatore/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:49:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/chicken-cacciatore/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  4 skinless, boneless chicken breasts, trimmed and sliced 1 tbsp dried italian seasoning 1 tsp sweet paprika 1 tsp salt 1/2 tsp black pepper 1/4 tsp crushed red pepper (Try it once before adding more) 1 tbsp olive oil 1 yellow bell pepper, sliced into strips 1 orange bell pepper, sliced into strips 1 onion, diced 3 cloves garlic, minced 1 (28 oz) jar pasta sauce 1 bay leaf 1/2 lb pasta, cooked according to directions fresh parsley (optional) parmesan cheese (optional)  Directions  Toss the chicken pieces with the italian seasoning, paprika, salt, pepper, red pepper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pappa Al Pomodoro</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/pappa-al-pomodoro/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:47:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/pappa-al-pomodoro/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  2 lb tomatoes, cored and quartered 2 garlic cloves, smashed 1/2 tsp fennel seeds 6 tbsp olive oil Kosher salt Black pepper 4 sprigs basil 1/4 loaf country style bread, crust removed torn into 2&amp;rdquo; pieces  Directions  Preheat oven to 450. Toss tomatoes, garlic, fennel, and 3 tbsp olive oil in a large baking dish. Season with salt and pepper. Roast, stirring occasionally, until the tomatoes are browned and the juices thicken, 30 to 35 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manga Kalan (Keralan Mango Curry) </title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/manga-kalan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:39:27 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/manga-kalan/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  2 3/4 c freshly grated or desiccated coconut 1/2 tbsp cumin seeds 4 small Thai green chiles or 2 serrano chiles, chopped 5 medium green mangoes, peeled and sliced 1 tbsp grated jaggery or light brown sugar 1 tsp cayenne 1 tsp ground turmeric Kosher salt to taste 1 1/4 c whole fat yogurt 2 tbsp coconut or canola oil 1/4 tsp brown mustard seeds 1/4 tsp fenugreek seeds 12 fresh or frozen curry leaves 3 dried chiles de arbol, stemmed and halved  Directions  Puree coconut, cumin, chiles, and 1 c water in a food processor until smooth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kill City Chili</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/kill-city-chili/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:37:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/kill-city-chili/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  3 tbsp olive oil 2 1/2 lbs ground beef 1/4 c dark chile powder 2 1/2 tbsp curry powder 3 cloves garlic, finely chopped 1 large yellow onion, diced 1 medium green bell pepper, diced 2 16 oz cans kideny beans, drained and rinsed 1 28 oz can crushed tomatoes Kosher salt and ground black pepper, to taste 3 tbsp chopped cilantro, plus more for garnish 1 c grated Monterey Jack cheese for serving Sour cream for serving  Directions  Heat oil in a 6 qt saucepan over medium high heat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feta Walnut Pasta</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/feta-walnut-pasta/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:26:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/feta-walnut-pasta/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  8 oz rotelle or fusilli pasta 1/2 c chopped walnuts 1 clove garlic, minced 1/2 c sliced green onions 1/3 c extra virgin olive oil 8 oz feta cheese, crumbled 5 oz sliced olives, drained 1/4 c chopped fresh basil  Directions  Cook pasta, and drain. Toast walnuts in a large non-stick skillet on medium high heat 5 minutes, stirring constantly. Remove walnuts from skillet, set aside. Cook and stir garlic and onions in oil on medium heat until tender.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chile Verde</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/chile-verde/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:08:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/chile-verde/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 1/2 pounds tomatillos 5 garlic cloves, not peeled 2 jalapenos, seeds and ribs removed, chopped 2 Anaheim or Poblano chiles (optional) 1 bunch cilantro leaves, cleaned and chopped 3 1/2 to 4 pounds pork shoulder (also called pork butt), trimmed of - excess fat and cut into 1 to 2-inch cubes Salt Freshly ground black pepper Olive oil 2 yellow onions, chopped 3 garlic cloves, peeled and finely chopped 2 Tbsp of chopped fresh oregano or 1 Tbsp of dried oregano 2 1/2 cups chicken stock Pinch of ground cloves  Directions  Remove papery husks from tomatillos and rinse well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Melting Pot Cheddar Cheese Fondue</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/cheddar-fondue/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 08:48:41 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/cheddar-fondue/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  6 oz medium sharp cheddar cheese 2 oz Emmenthaler Swiss cheese 4 oz Coors Light 2 tsp chopped garlic 2 tsp Worcestershire sauce 2 Tbsp flour 2 tsp dry mustard powder  Directions  If you are using a fondue pot, turn it onto medium heat Otherwise, use a double boiler to heat the mixture. Combine beer, garlic, mustard powder, and Worcestershire sauce. Shred or cube all cheese, and toss with flour coating the cheese well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buffalo Sauce</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/buffalo-sauce/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 07:11:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/buffalo-sauce/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  2/3 cup hot pepper sauce (Frank&#39;s RedHot) 1/2 cup cold unsalted butter 1 1/2 tablespoons white vinegar 1/4 teaspoon Worcestershire sauce 1/4 teaspoon cayenne pepper 1/8 teaspoon garlic powder salt to taste  Directions  Combine the hot sauce, butter, vinegar, Worcestershire sauce, cayenne pepper, garlic powder, and salt in a pot and place over medium heat. Bring to a simmer while stirring with a whisk. As soon as the liquid begins to bubble on the sides of the pot, remove from heat, stir with the whisk, and set aside for use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Braised Balsamic Chicken</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/braised-balsamic-chicken/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 07:11:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/braised-balsamic-chicken/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  6 skinless, boneless chicken breast halves ground black pepper 1 tsp garlic salt 2 tbsp olive oil 1 onion, thinly sliced 1/2 c balsamic vinegar 1 (14.5 oz) can diced tomatoes 1 tsp dried basil 1 tsp dried oregano 1 tsp dried rosemary 1/2 tsp dried thyme  Directions  Season chicken breasts with black pepper and garlic salt. Heat olive oil in medium skillet. Brown the onion and seasoned chicken breasts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balsamic Roast Beef</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/balsamic-roast-beef/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 07:01:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/balsamic-roast-beef/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  3 – 4 lb chuck roast 1 c beef broth 1/2 c balsamic vinegar 1 tbsp Worcestershire sauce 1 tbsp soy sauce 1 tbsp honey 1/2 tsp red pepper flakes 4 cloves minced garlic  Directions  Place beef in slow cooker. Combine other ingredients in a mixing bowl and pour over the beef. Cook on high 4 hours or low for 6 to 8 hours. (Optional) Reduce the drippings in a saucepan to concentrate the flavor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweet Potato Black Bean Chili</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/sweet-potato-black-bean-chili/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 18:05:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/sweet-potato-black-bean-chili/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  2 lbs sweet potatoes, peeled and cubed 1/2 tsp ground dried chipotle pepper 1/2 tsp salt 2 tbsp olive oil 1 onion, diced 4 cloves garlic, minced 1 red bell pepper, diced 1 jalapeno pepper, sliced 2 tbsp ancho chile powder, or to taste 1 tbsp ground cumin 1/4 tsp dried oregano 1 (28 oz) can diced tomatoes 1 c water, or more as needed 1 tbsp cornmeal 1 tsp salt, or to taste 1 tsp white sugar 1 tsp unsweetened cocoa powder 2 (15 oz) cans black beans, washed and drained 1 pinch cayenne pepper 1/2 c sour cream for garnish (optional) 1/4 c chopped fresh cilantro (optional)  Directions  Preheat oven to 400 degrees.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>