<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Laura McGowan on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</title>
    <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/author/laura-mcgowan/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Laura McGowan on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 09:06:52 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bstreete.github.io/public/author/laura-mcgowan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Justin Wilson Barbeque Ham</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/justin-wilson-bbq-ham/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 09:06:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/justin-wilson-bbq-ham/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  8 to 10 pound ham (pre-cooked) 3 cloves garlic 3 jalapeño peppers barbeque sauce 6 green onions  Directions  Sliver the onion, garlic, and jalapeños. With a sharp knife, make a deep X into the ham (6 times, space the holes evenly). In each hole, stuff one piece of green onion, 1/2 of a garlic clove, and 1/2 of a jalapeño. Pour barbeque sauce over ham, leaving roughly 1&amp;rdquo; in the bottom of the pan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>White Lasagna</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/white-lasagna/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 08:59:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/white-lasagna/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  8oz lasagna noodles 1 pound ground beef 1 cup finely chopped celery 3/4 finely chopped onion 2 teaspoon dried basil 1 teaspoon dried oregano 2 cup shredded gouda 12 oz mozzerella 1 cup shredded cheddar 1/2 teaspoon Italian seasoning 1 cup light cream (half and half) 3 oz cubed cream cheese 1 clove garlic, minced 1/2 cup white wine 1 egg, slightly beaten 12 oz creamy style cottage cheese (1 1/2 cups) salt and pepper to taste  Directions  In a large skillet, cook ground beef, celery, onion, and garlic until meat is browned and veggies are tender.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Muffulettas</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/muffulettas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 07:56:25 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/muffulettas/</guid>
      <description>Pronounced moof-uh-leh-tuh
Ingredients Sandwich Ingredients  1 round loaf of soft Italian bread (any crusty top roll) olive oil 3 slices baked ham; turkey is an acceptable substitute 3 slices provolone cheese 3 slices swiss cheese 6 slices genoa salame 4 tablespoons olive salad  Olive Salad Ingredients  1/2 cup spanish olives with pimentos, chopped 1/2 cup black olives, chopped 1/2 cup finely chopped celery 1/4 cup finely chopped carrots 1 tablespoon parsley 1 tablespoon green pepper, chopped 1 tablespoon minced onion 1 cup olive oil 1/2 cup vegetable oil 1/2 teaspoon oregano 1/2 teaspoon black pepper  Directions Sandwich Directions  Split bread on the round and brush with oilve oil.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>