<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Recipes on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</title>
    <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Recipes on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2019 12:31:07 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cross Rib Roast</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/rib-roast/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2019 12:31:07 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/rib-roast/</guid>
      <description>Source: Genius Kitchen
Ingredients  2 pounds cross-rib roast 2 tablespoons balsamic vinegar 2 tablespoons minced garlic 2 teaspoons dried thyme 1 teaspoon dried rosemary 1 tablespoon salt 1 teaspoon pepper 1 tablespoon olive oil  Directions  Brush roast with balsamic vinegar. Make a paste with remaining ingredients and apply to meat. Roast meat at 450 for 15 minutes. Reduce heat to 350 and cook for 40 to 60 minutes, or until internal temperature reaches 125.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Authentic Louisiana Red Beans and Rice</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/red-beans-rice/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 17:17:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/red-beans-rice/</guid>
      <description>Source: All Recipes by Miami Beach
Note: Can cook in a slow cooker with two cans of prepared kidney beans for four to six hours on low.
Ingredients  1 pound dry kidney beans 1/4 cup olive oil 1 large onion, chopped 1 green bell pepper, chopped 2 tablespoons minced garlic 2 stalks celery, chopped 6 cups water 2 bay leaves 1/2 teaspoon cayenne pepper 1 teaspoon dried thyme 1/4 teaspoon dried sage 1 tablespoon dried parsley 1 teaspoon Cajun seasoning 1 pound andouille sausage, sliced 4 cups water 2 cups long grain white rice  Directions  Rinse beans, and then soak in a large pot of water overnight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homemade Falafel with Tahini Sauce</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/falafel-with-tahini/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 17:14:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/falafel-with-tahini/</guid>
      <description>Source: Just a Taste
Ingredients Falafel  2 cups roughly chopped white onion 6 garlic cloves 2 cups cooked chickpeas, drained 1 cup lightly packed parsley leaves 1 cup lightly packed cilantro leaves 1 teaspoon salt 1/4 teaspoon chili powder 2 teaspoons cumin 2 teaspoons baking powder 1/2 cup all-purpose flour Canola oil, for sauteing Pita bread, for serving  Tahini Sauce  1/4 cups plain yogurt (full fat or non-fat) /4 cup tahini (sesame paste) Tablespoons fresh lemon juice  Directions  Add the onion and garlic cloves to the bowl of a food processor and pulse just until they are finely minced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Potatoes, Peppers, and Kielbasa Skillet</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/kielbasa-potatoes-peppers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 17:09:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/kielbasa-potatoes-peppers/</guid>
      <description>Source: My Life Cookbook
Ingredients  3 Tablespoons olive oil 3 potatoes chopped 2 sweet bell peppers chopped 1 onion chopped 14 oz kielbasa sliced 1/2 teaspoon salt 1/4 teaspoon pepper 1/4 teaspoon oregano 1/4 basil 1 teaspoon crushed garlic  Directions  Preheat oven to 375 degrees. Using 1 Tablespoon of olive oil, spread all over a cast iron or oven proof skillet. In a large bowl add your vegetables and kielbasa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Not) Butter Chicken</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/not-butter-chicken/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 15:04:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/not-butter-chicken/</guid>
      <description>Source: Budget Bytes
Ingredients  1.25 lbs. 2 lg chicken breasts 3 Tbsp butter 3 cloves garlic 1 med onion 1 inch fresh ginger 1 Tbsp garam masala 1/4 tsp cayenne pepper 1 15 oz. can tomato sauce 1 15 oz. can diced tomatoes 1/2 cup plain yogurt 1 1/2 cups jasmine or basmati rice 2 1/4 cups water  Directions  Trim the fat from the chicken breasts and cut them into small chunks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>La Taqueria Carnitas</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/carnitas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 15:02:36 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/carnitas/</guid>
      <description>Source: Sunset
Ingredients  1 boned, tied pork shoulder or butt (4 to 5 lb.) 2 onions (1 lb. total), peeled and quartered 4 stalks celery (including leaves), rinsed and cut into chunks 4 cloves garlic, peeled 2 dried bay leaves 2 teaspoons dried thyme About 1 teaspoon salt 1/2 cup milk  Directions  Rinse pork and put in a 6- to 8-quart pan. Add onions, celery, garlic, bay leaves, thyme, 1 teaspoon salt, and enough water to cover meat&amp;ndash;2 1/2 to 3 1/2 quarts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Instant Pot Mac and Cheese</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/instant-pot-mac-and-cheese/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 15:00:34 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/instant-pot-mac-and-cheese/</guid>
      <description>Source: I Don&#39;t Have Time for That!
Ingredients  1 lb Elbow Noodles 1 Cup Guinness Beer 3 Cups Water 2 Tablespoons Butter 1 Tablespoon Dry Mustard Powder 2 Ounces Cream Cheese cut into cubes 1 Can Eveporated Milk 1/2 Teaspoon Salt 1/2 Teaspoon Pepper or to taste 14 Ounces Kerrygold Irish Cheddar 2 bricks 1 Cup Monterey Jack Cheese  Directions  Add beer, water, noodles, butter, mustard powder, salt and pepper to Instant Pot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Better than Takeout Ham Fried Rice</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/ham-fried-rice/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 14:58:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/ham-fried-rice/</guid>
      <description>Source: The Recipe Critic
Ingredients  1½ cups- 2 cups chopped ham 3 cups cooked rice 2 Tbs sesame oil 1 small white onion, chopped 1 cup frozen peas and carrots, thawed 2-3 Tablespoons soy sauce (more or less to taste) 3 eggs, lightly beaten 2 Tbsp chopped green onions (optional)  Directions  Preheat a large skillet or wok to medium heat. Pour sesame oil in the bottom. Add white onion, chopped ham, peas and carrots and fry until tender.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lentil &amp; Sausage Stew</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/lentil-sausage-stew/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 14:55:13 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/lentil-sausage-stew/</guid>
      <description>Source: Budget Bytes
Ingredients  1/2 lb Italian sausage 1 medium onion 3 medium carrots (1/2 lb) 4 stalks celery (1/2 bunch) 2 cloves garlic 2 cups brown lentils 6 cups chicken broth 1/2 tsp cayenne 1 tsp smoked paprika 1 tsp cumin 1 tsp oregano 10 oz frozen spinach  Directions  Brown the sausage in a large pot over medium heat, breaking it up into pieces as it cooks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Potato Soup with Bacon and Cheddar</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/potato-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 14:52:05 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/potato-soup/</guid>
      <description>Source: Emeril
Ingredients  4 strips bacon, diced 2 cups chopped yellow onion 1/4 cup minced shallot 1 tablespoon minced garlic 2 1/2 pounds Idaho potatoes, peeled and cut into 1/2-inch dice, reserved in a bowl of cold water 5 cups chicken stock or canned, low-sodium chicken broth 3/4 teaspoon salt 1/4 teaspoon ground white pepper 1/4 teaspoon ground black pepper, plus more for garnish 1/2 cup heavy cream 2 tablespoons chopped green onion tops, plus more for garnish 8 ounces grated sharp Cheddar, for garnish (recommend doubling)  Note: Can use broccoli instead of bacon, and olive oil instead of bacon grease for a lighter soup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Serbian Ground Beef, Veggie, and Potato Bake</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/serbian-beef-potato-bake/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 14:50:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/serbian-beef-potato-bake/</guid>
      <description>Source: All Recipes by amanda1432
Ingredients  1 pound ground beef 1 tablespoon olive oil 1 green bell pepper, chopped 1 onion, chopped 1 carrot, shredded 2 celery stalks, chopped 1/2 tablespoon paprika 1/2 teaspoon salt 3/4 teaspoon black pepper 1/4 teaspoon crushed red pepper 1 pinch ground cinnamon 1 pinch ground cloves 1/4 cup water 1/8 cup red wine 1 cube beef bouillon 2 tablespoons half-and-half 2 potatoes, peeled and sliced  Directions  Preheat oven to 400 degrees F (200 degrees C).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple Green-Chile Pie With Cheddar Crust</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/green-chile-apple-pie/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 14:46:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/green-chile-apple-pie/</guid>
      <description>Source: New York Times
Ingredients Crust  1 ¼ cups all-purpose flour ¼ teaspoon salt ⅓ cup cold unsalted butter, cut into dice ½ cup grated sharp Cheddar cheese 5 tablespoons ice water, more as needed  Filling  5 cups peeled and thickly sliced tart apples, such as Jonagold, Honeycrisp or Granny Smith ½ cup chopped roasted green Hatch chilies, mild or medium hot (see note) 2 tablespoons fresh lemon juice ½ cup granulated sugar ¼ cup light brown sugar ½ teaspoon cinnamon ¼ teaspoon allspice ¼ teaspoon nutmeg, preferably freshly grated ¼ teaspoon salt ¼ cup cornstarch  Topping  ½ cup all-purpose flour ½ cup finely chopped walnuts ¼ cup light brown sugar 4 tablespoons unsalted butter, melted Vanilla ice cream, for serving  Directions  Make the crust: In a food processor or mixer fitted with a paddle attachment, combine flour and salt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roasted Butternut Squash Soup</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/butternut-squash-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 14:49:43 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/butternut-squash-soup/</guid>
      <description>Source: The Garden Kitchen
Ingredients  1 Large (2 to 3 pound) butternut squash 1 tablespoon olive oil salt and pepper to taste 1 onion, roughly chopped 1 tablespoon chopped fresh sage 3 garlic cloves, roasted 4 cups vegetable broth 1/4 cup toasted pumpkin seeds (optional)  Directions  Preheat oven to 400°F. Line or grease a baking sheet. Cut the squash in half lengthwise and remove the seeds. Place on the baking sheet, brush with olive oil, and sprinkle with salt and pepper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kale Salad with Mustard Vinaigrette</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/kale-salad-mustard-vinaigrette/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 14:39:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/kale-salad-mustard-vinaigrette/</guid>
      <description>Source: The Garden Kitchen
Ingredients Salad  Medium bunch of kale (best with Lacinto aka &amp;lsquo;Dinosaur&amp;rsquo; kale) 1/2 cup pecan or walnut pieces 1/2 cup dried cherries or cranberries 1/4 cup queso fresco or soft goat cheese 1/2 cup Mustard Vinaigrette  Mustard Vinaigrette Dressing  1/2 small red onion, chopped finely (roughly 1/4 cup) 2 tablespoons rice wine vinegar 1 tablespoon Dijon mustard 1/4 teaspoon salt 1/2 teaspoon pepper 2/3 cup olive oil  Directions Salad  Wash kale and pat dry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crepes</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/crepes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 10:02:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/crepes/</guid>
      <description>Source: Veronica Bower&#39;s French family
Ingredients  1 cup flour 1 cup milk 1/4 cup sugar (for dinner crepes (ex: ham &amp;amp; cheese), decrease sugar by 1/2) 4 eggs 1 tablespoon oil  Directions  Mix flour, milk, sugar, eggs, and oil in bowl. Batter should be runny. Heat medium size nonstick frying pan to medium heat. Spray pan with cooking spray (only on first crepe). Place 1/4 cup batter in pan an switch around until bottom is covered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweet Potato Pancakes</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/sweet-potato-pancakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 10:00:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/sweet-potato-pancakes/</guid>
      <description>Source: The Garden Kitchen
Ingredients  1 pound sweet potatoes (about 2 medium), peeled and coarsely grated 2 scallions, finely chopped 1/3 cup all-purpose flour 2 large eggs, lightly beaten 1 teaspoon salt 1/2 teaspoon black pepper 1/2 teaspoon powdered garlic 1/2 teaspoon ground cumin 2 tablespoons vegetable oil  Directions  Wash hands with soap and warm water. Wash produce well and chop as directed. Stir together all ingredients, except oil, until well mixed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meaty Beany Chili</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/meaty-beany-chili/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:59:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/meaty-beany-chili/</guid>
      <description>Source: The PPK
Ingredients  1 tablespoon olive oil 1 yellow onion, diced medium 1 green pepper, seeded, diced medium 6 cloves garlic, minced 2 jalapenos, thinly sliced (seeded, if you want it less - spicy) 3 to 4 tablespoons mild chili powder 1 tablespoon dried mexican oregano 2 teaspoons ground cumin 1 1/2 teaspoons salt Several dashes fresh black pepper 1/8th teaspoon ground cloves 2 cups water (plus extra as needed) - stock is an acceptable substitute 1 cup dried brown lentils 1 28 oz can crushed tomatoes 1 1/2 cups cooked kidney beans, rinsed and drained (15 oz - can) 1 1/2 cups cooked black beans, rinsed and drained (15 oz - can) 1 tablespoon pure maple syrup 2 tablespoons lime juice  Directions  Set your slow cooker to “sear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Italian Sausage with Potatoes and Peppers </title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/italian-sausage-potatoes-peppers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:58:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/italian-sausage-potatoes-peppers/</guid>
      <description>Source: Robyn Dafoe
Ingredients  1 1/2 pounds Italian sausage 3 to 5 Russet potatoes 3 green peppers 1/4 cup water Salt and pepper to taste 1 onion  Directions  Preheat oven to 400°. Slice potatoes thin and layer on bottom of baking dish. Season potatoes. Thinly slice peppers and onions; layer over the potatoes before seasoning. Crumble uncooked sausage over the vegetables. Pour water into baking dish; cover dish with foil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baked French Toast</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/baked-french-toast/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:56:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/baked-french-toast/</guid>
      <description>Source: Lis Handley
Ingredients  Loaf of French bread 3 eggs 3 tablespoons sugar 1 teaspoon vanilla 2 1/4 cup milk 1/2 cup flour 6 tablespoons brown sugar 1/2 teaspoon cinnamon 1/4 cup butter 1 cup berries  Directions  Cut bread diagonally. Place in baking dish. Beat eggs, sugard, and vanilla together. Stir in milk and pour over bread. Turn slices to coat well. Cover and refrigerate at least two hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chipotle Crema</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/chipotle-crema/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:55:27 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/chipotle-crema/</guid>
      <description>Source: The Garden Kitchen
Ingredients  1/2 cup low fat Greek yogurt 1 tablespoon of sauce from chipotle chili peppers in adobo 1 teaspoon lime juice 1/2 teaspoon honey pinch of salt  Directions  Wash hands with soap and warm water. Place all ingredients in a samll bowl and stir until smooth. Taste and add more lime, chipotle, or honey if needed. Serve cold on sandwiches, wraps, or hamburgers. Keeps for up to one week in a sealed container in the refrigerator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2am Chili</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/2am-chili/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:53:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/2am-chili/</guid>
      <description>Source: r/pics
Ingredients  2 tablespoons flour 1 teaspoon basil 1 tablespoon onion powder 4 teaspoons chili powder 2 teaspoons cumin 1 tablespoon cayenne 1 tablespoon garlic powder 2 teaspoons sugar 3 to 4 cloves of garlic 1 onion 1 bell pepper 1 1/2 pounds of ground beef 1 15oz can of tomato sauce 1 15oz can of diced tomatoes 1 15oz can of corn 1 15oz can of kidney beans 1 can of beer (optional)  Directions  Brown the beef in a skillet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Classic Spritz Cookies </title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/spritz-cookies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:51:41 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/spritz-cookies/</guid>
      <description>Source: Wilton Home 
Ingredients  3 1/2 c all purpose flour 1 tsp baking powder 1 1/2 cups softened butter 1 c granulated sugar 1 egg 2 Tbsp milk 1 tsp clear vanilla extract 1/2 tsp no-color almond extract  Directions  Preheat oven to 350. Combine flour and baking powder. In large bowl, beat butter and sugar with electric mixer until light and fluffy. Add egg, milk, vanilla, and almond extract; mix well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slow Cooker Chicken Cacciatore </title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/chicken-cacciatore/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:49:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/chicken-cacciatore/</guid>
      <description>Source: Kitchen Concoctions 
Ingredients  4 skinless, boneless chicken breasts, trimmed and sliced 1 tbsp dried italian seasoning 1 tsp sweet paprika 1 tsp salt 1/2 tsp black pepper 1/4 tsp crushed red pepper (Try it once before adding more) 1 tbsp olive oil 1 yellow bell pepper, sliced into strips 1 orange bell pepper, sliced into strips 1 onion, diced 3 cloves garlic, minced 1 (28 oz) jar pasta sauce 1 bay leaf 1/2 lb pasta, cooked according to directions fresh parsley (optional) parmesan cheese (optional)  Directions  Toss the chicken pieces with the italian seasoning, paprika, salt, pepper, red pepper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crispy Salt and Vinegar Potatoes</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/salt-vinegar-potatoes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:48:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/salt-vinegar-potatoes/</guid>
      <description>Source: Bon Appetit August 2014
Ingredients  2 lb. Baby Yukon Gold potatoes, halved, quartered if large 1 cup plus 2 Tbsp distilled white vinegar 1 Tbsp kosher salt, plus more 2 Tbsp unsalted butter Ground black pepper 2 Tbsp chopped fresh chives Flaky sea salt  Directions  Combine potatoes, 1 cup of vinegar, and 1 Tbsp kosher salt in a medium saucepan; add water to cover by 1&amp;rdquo;. Bring to a boil, reduce heat, and simmer ntil potatoes are tender, 20 - 25 minutes; drain and pat dry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pappa Al Pomodoro</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/pappa-al-pomodoro/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:47:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/pappa-al-pomodoro/</guid>
      <description>Source: Bon Appetit August 2014
Ingredients  2 lb tomatoes, cored and quartered 2 garlic cloves, smashed 1/2 tsp fennel seeds 6 tbsp olive oil Kosher salt Black pepper 4 sprigs basil 1/4 loaf country style bread, crust removed torn into 2&amp;rdquo; pieces  Directions  Preheat oven to 450. Toss tomatoes, garlic, fennel, and 3 tbsp olive oil in a large baking dish. Season with salt and pepper. Roast, stirring occasionally, until the tomatoes are browned and the juices thicken, 30 to 35 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wry Braid (Onion Bread) </title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/onion-bread/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:45:44 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/onion-bread/</guid>
      <description>Source: Tracy Handley
Ingredients  2 packages active dry yeast 2 cups warm water 1 envelope onion soup mix 1/3 c sugar 2 tbsp molasses 1 tsp salt 1 egg 1/3 c soft shortening 6 to 6 1/2 c flour (not self-rising)  Directions  In mixing bowl, dissolve yeast in warm water. Add soup mix, stir to dissolve completely. Add remaining ingredients, but only half of the flour. Beat with a spoon until smooth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Knead Herb Bread</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/no-knead-herb-bread/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:40:54 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/no-knead-herb-bread/</guid>
      <description>Source: All Recipes
Ingredients  3 c all purpose flour 1 tsp salt 1 tbsp sugar 1 (2 1/2 tsp) package active dry yeast 1 1/4 c warm water 2 tbsp shortening or softened butter 3 tsp dried sage 1/2 tsp dried rosemary 1/4 tsp dried thyme 1 tsp melted butter  Directions  Combine 2 cups flour, salt, sugar, and yeast in a large bowl. Stir in the water, shortening, sage, rosemary, and thyme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manga Kalan (Keralan Mango Curry) </title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/manga-kalan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:39:27 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/manga-kalan/</guid>
      <description>Source: Saveur Issue 162
Ingredients  2 3/4 c freshly grated or desiccated coconut 1/2 tbsp cumin seeds 4 small Thai green chiles or 2 serrano chiles, chopped 5 medium green mangoes, peeled and sliced 1 tbsp grated jaggery or light brown sugar 1 tsp cayenne 1 tsp ground turmeric Kosher salt to taste 1 1/4 c whole fat yogurt 2 tbsp coconut or canola oil 1/4 tsp brown mustard seeds 1/4 tsp fenugreek seeds 12 fresh or frozen curry leaves 3 dried chiles de arbol, stemmed and halved  Directions  Puree coconut, cumin, chiles, and 1 c water in a food processor until smooth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kill City Chili</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/kill-city-chili/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:37:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/kill-city-chili/</guid>
      <description>Source: Saveur Issue 162 
Ingredients  3 tbsp olive oil 2 1/2 lbs ground beef 1/4 c dark chile powder 2 1/2 tbsp curry powder 3 cloves garlic, finely chopped 1 large yellow onion, diced 1 medium green bell pepper, diced 2 16 oz cans kideny beans, drained and rinsed 1 28 oz can crushed tomatoes Kosher salt and ground black pepper, to taste 3 tbsp chopped cilantro, plus more for garnish 1 c grated Monterey Jack cheese for serving Sour cream for serving  Directions  Heat oil in a 6 qt saucepan over medium high heat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greek Salad with Walnuts </title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/greek-salad-walnuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:29:54 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/greek-salad-walnuts/</guid>
      <description>Source: Athenos and Colavita Ad
Ingredients Salad  1 package (10 oz) mixed salad greens 1 c ripe olives 3 plum tomatoes cut into wedges 1 small red onion, thinly sliced 1/2 medium cucumber, peeled, cut into wedges 1/2 c coarsely chopped walnuts 8 oz feta cheese  Dressing  1/2 c Extra Virgin Olive Oil 1/4 c lemon juice 1 clove garlic, minced 1 tsp dried oregano leaves 1/4 tsp pepper 1/4 tsp salt  Directions  Mix salad dressings together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feta Walnut Pasta</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/feta-walnut-pasta/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:26:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/feta-walnut-pasta/</guid>
      <description>Source: Athenos and Colavita Ad
Ingredients  8 oz rotelle or fusilli pasta 1/2 c chopped walnuts 1 clove garlic, minced 1/2 c sliced green onions 1/3 c extra virgin olive oil 8 oz feta cheese, crumbled 5 oz sliced olives, drained 1/4 c chopped fresh basil  Directions  Cook pasta, and drain. Toast walnuts in a large non-stick skillet on medium high heat 5 minutes, stirring constantly. Remove walnuts from skillet, set aside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Savory Feta Cheese Log with Toasted Walnuts and Olives</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/feta-cheese-log/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:26:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/feta-cheese-log/</guid>
      <description>Source: Athenos and Colavita Ad
Ingredients  8 oz feta cheese, crumbled 4 oz cream cheese, softened 1 clove garlic, minced 2 tbsp extra virgin olive oil 1/4 c chopped olives 2 tbsp sliced green onions 1/2 c chopped walnuts  Directions  Mix feta cheese, cream cheese, and oil with electric mixer on medium speed until well blended. Add olives and onions, mix well. Toast walnuts in a large non-stick skillet on medium-high heat 5 minutes, stirring constantly, cool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easy Pizza Dough</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/easy-pizza-dough/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:23:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/easy-pizza-dough/</guid>
      <description>Source: Betty Crocker
Ingredients  1 c warm water 1 package of yeast 1 tsp salt 2 1/2 c of flour 2 Tbsp olive oil  Directions  Dissolve yeast in warm water Mix in flour, salt, and oil in 20 hard strokes. (Don&#39;t overmix) Let rest 20 minutes. Flour your hands, and divide into two portions. On an oiled and cornmealed pan, pat the dough into an ~ 11 in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doug&#39;s Home Made Salsa</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/dougs-salsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:21:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/dougs-salsa/</guid>
      <description>Source: Doug Silhacek
Ingredients  1/3 bunch of cilantro 1/2 small white onion 2 cloves of garlic 1 can diced fire roasted tomatoes 1 small can of diced green chiles 1/2 tsp of ground oregano 1/2 tsp black pepper Dash of salt Dash of ground cayenne pepper Dash of red pepper flake Juice of 1/2 a lime  Directions  Combine in food processor and chop to desired consistency.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Herby Corn Salad</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/corn-salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:19:02 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/corn-salad/</guid>
      <description>Source: Bon Appetit August 2014
Ingredients  1/4 c olive oil 2 tbsp sherry vinegar salt pepper 1 sliced small shallot 1/2 c torn fresh herbs (like dill, mint, and/or - chives) 3 c raw or blanched corn kernels  Directions  Whisk olive oil and vinegar in a large bowl. Season with salt and pepper, add the shallot and herbs. Fold in the corn kernels, and season with salt and pepper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corn Jalapeno Fritters</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/corn-jalapeno-fritters/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:12:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/corn-jalapeno-fritters/</guid>
      <description>Source: Bon Appetit August 2014
Ingredients  2 beaten large eggs 1/4 c all purpose flour 2 tbsp grated parmesan 1/2 tsp kosher salt 2 c fresh corn kernels 1 thinly sliced scallion 1/2 finely chopped jalapeno 2 tbsp vegetable oil Sour cream (optional) Lime wedges (optional)  Directions  Pulse eggs, flour, parmesan, and kosher salt in a food processor to combine. Add corn, scallion, and jalapeno. Pulse 2 to 3 times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chile Verde</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/chile-verde/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:08:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/chile-verde/</guid>
      <description>Source: Simply Recipes
Ingredients  1 1/2 pounds tomatillos 5 garlic cloves, not peeled 2 jalapenos, seeds and ribs removed, chopped 2 Anaheim or Poblano chiles (optional) 1 bunch cilantro leaves, cleaned and chopped 3 1/2 to 4 pounds pork shoulder (also called pork butt), trimmed of - excess fat and cut into 1 to 2-inch cubes Salt Freshly ground black pepper Olive oil 2 yellow onions, chopped 3 garlic cloves, peeled and finely chopped 2 Tbsp of chopped fresh oregano or 1 Tbsp of dried oregano 2 1/2 cups chicken stock Pinch of ground cloves  Directions  Remove papery husks from tomatillos and rinse well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fresno Chile Hot Sauce</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/chile-hot-sauce/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:06:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/chile-hot-sauce/</guid>
      <description>Source: Bon Appetit August 2014
Ingredients  1/2 lb stemmed Fresno chiles (8 - 10) 6 peeled garlic cloves 3 tbsp red wine vinegar Salt, to taste  Directions  Cook chiles and garlic in large saucepan of boiling salted water until chiles turn red, about 2 minutes. Drain. Blend chiles, garlic, and vinegar in a blender until almost smooth. Season with salt and let cool. Can be made a week ahead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheesecake</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/cheesecake/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:04:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/cheesecake/</guid>
      <description>Source: Unknown
Ingredients  1 graham (or other) crust 2 pkg cream cheese 1/3 c sugar 1 tbls milk 1 tbls vanilla 1 egg  Directions  Mix everything but the crust together. Pour the mix into the crust. Bake in a preheated oven at 350 for 30 minutes. Let cool and enjoy.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Melting Pot Cheddar Cheese Fondue</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/cheddar-fondue/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 08:48:41 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/cheddar-fondue/</guid>
      <description>Source: CopyKat Recipes
Ingredients  6 oz medium sharp cheddar cheese 2 oz Emmenthaler Swiss cheese 4 oz Coors Light 2 tsp chopped garlic 2 tsp Worcestershire sauce 2 Tbsp flour 2 tsp dry mustard powder  Directions  If you are using a fondue pot, turn it onto medium heat Otherwise, use a double boiler to heat the mixture. Combine beer, garlic, mustard powder, and Worcestershire sauce. Shred or cube all cheese, and toss with flour coating the cheese well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cauliflower Gratinee</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/cauliflower-gratinee/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 07:11:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/cauliflower-gratinee/</guid>
      <description>Source: Joy of Cooking
Ingredients  6 tbsp unsalted butter 4 cloves garlic, minced 4 oz thinly sliced prosciutto, cut into thin strips Florets of 1 large head cauliflower, cut into 1/4 in lengthwise- slices 2 tbsp unbleached all purpose flour 1 1/2 c heavy or whipping cream Pinch cayenne pepper Salt and freshly ground black pper, to taste 1 1/2 c grated Swiss cheese 1/2 c chopped fresh parsley  Directions  Preheat oven to 350.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buffalo Sauce</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/buffalo-sauce/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 07:11:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/buffalo-sauce/</guid>
      <description>Source: AllRecipes by Chef John
Ingredients  2/3 cup hot pepper sauce (Frank&#39;s RedHot) 1/2 cup cold unsalted butter 1 1/2 tablespoons white vinegar 1/4 teaspoon Worcestershire sauce 1/4 teaspoon cayenne pepper 1/8 teaspoon garlic powder salt to taste  Directions  Combine the hot sauce, butter, vinegar, Worcestershire sauce, cayenne pepper, garlic powder, and salt in a pot and place over medium heat. Bring to a simmer while stirring with a whisk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Braised Balsamic Chicken</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/braised-balsamic-chicken/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 07:11:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/braised-balsamic-chicken/</guid>
      <description>Source: All Recipes by MoonAndBack
Ingredients  6 skinless, boneless chicken breast halves ground black pepper 1 tsp garlic salt 2 tbsp olive oil 1 onion, thinly sliced 1/2 c balsamic vinegar 1 (14.5 oz) can diced tomatoes 1 tsp dried basil 1 tsp dried oregano 1 tsp dried rosemary 1/2 tsp dried thyme  Directions  Season chicken breasts with black pepper and garlic salt. Heat olive oil in medium skillet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blackberry Vinegar Caramel</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/blackberry-vinegar-caramel/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 07:11:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/blackberry-vinegar-caramel/</guid>
      <description>Source: Bon Appetit May 2014 Issue
Ingredients  1 c sugar 1/4 c unseasoned rice vinegar 10 oz fresh or frozen blackberries (can use raspberries instead)  Directions  Cook sugar in a medium saucepan over medium heat without stirring, until it begins to turn golden brown around the edges. Stir to incorporate melted sugar and cook, stirring occasionally, until all sugar is melted and caramel turns a deep amber color, 6 to 8 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balsamic Roast Beef</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/balsamic-roast-beef/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 07:01:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/balsamic-roast-beef/</guid>
      <description>Source: AddAPinch.com
Ingredients  3 – 4 lb chuck roast 1 c beef broth 1/2 c balsamic vinegar 1 tbsp Worcestershire sauce 1 tbsp soy sauce 1 tbsp honey 1/2 tsp red pepper flakes 4 cloves minced garlic  Directions  Place beef in slow cooker. Combine other ingredients in a mixing bowl and pour over the beef. Cook on high 4 hours or low for 6 to 8 hours. (Optional) Reduce the drippings in a saucepan to concentrate the flavor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweet Potato Black Bean Chili</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/sweet-potato-black-bean-chili/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 18:05:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/sweet-potato-black-bean-chili/</guid>
      <description>Source: AllRecipes by Chef John
Ingredients  2 lbs sweet potatoes, peeled and cubed 1/2 tsp ground dried chipotle pepper 1/2 tsp salt 2 tbsp olive oil 1 onion, diced 4 cloves garlic, minced 1 red bell pepper, diced 1 jalapeno pepper, sliced 2 tbsp ancho chile powder, or to taste 1 tbsp ground cumin 1/4 tsp dried oregano 1 (28 oz) can diced tomatoes 1 c water, or more as needed 1 tbsp cornmeal 1 tsp salt, or to taste 1 tsp white sugar 1 tsp unsweetened cocoa powder 2 (15 oz) cans black beans, washed and drained 1 pinch cayenne pepper 1/2 c sour cream for garnish (optional) 1/4 c chopped fresh cilantro (optional)  Directions  Preheat oven to 400 degrees.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>