<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tracy Handley on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</title>
    <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/author/tracy-handley/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tracy Handley on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 07:52:09 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bstreete.github.io/public/author/tracy-handley/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dill Cottage Cheese Bread</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/dill-cottage-cheese-bread/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 07:52:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/dill-cottage-cheese-bread/</guid>
      <description>Notes  Can omit the dill for a wonderful, simple white bread.  Ingredients  1 package dry yeast 1/4 cup warm water 1 cup creamed cottage cheese 2 tablespoons sugar 1 tablespoon minced onion 1 teaspoon dill seed 1 teaspoon salt 1/4 teaspoon baking soda 1 egg beaten 2 1/4 to 2 1/2 cups flour 1/4 cup shortening  Directions  In a large bowl, dissolve the yeast in warm water.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perfect Sauce or Gravy Base</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/perfect-sauce-gravy-base/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 09:26:32 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/perfect-sauce-gravy-base/</guid>
      <description>Base Ingredients  3 tablespoons of fat (ex: butter or grease) 3 tablespoons of flour 2 cups liquid (ex: stock or milk)  Sauce  Add green chile  Gravy  Use stock for the liquid  Gravy for Biscuits  Use bacon grease for fat and milk for liquid  Directions  In a sauce pan, heat the fat. Whisk in flour until well combined and no unincorporated flour remains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Picatta</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/chicken-picatta/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 08:07:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/chicken-picatta/</guid>
      <description>Recommend serving over angelhair pasta with a side of roasted asparagus.
Ingredients  chicken breasts flour, seasoned with salt and pepper white wine lemon juice butter 2 tablespoons capers olive oil  Directions  Pound chicken to desired thinness. Dredge in flour. Saute dredged chicken in a half olive oil, half butter mixture until golden. Move chicken to plate. Slowly pour wine into pan to deglaze. Add lemon juice to taste (be generous).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wry Braid (Onion Bread)</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/onion-bread/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:45:44 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/onion-bread/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  2 packages active dry yeast 2 cups warm water 1 envelope onion soup mix 1/3 c sugar 2 tbsp molasses 1 tsp salt 1 egg 1/3 c soft shortening 6 to 6 1/2 c flour (not self-rising)  Directions  In mixing bowl, dissolve yeast in warm water. Add soup mix, stir to dissolve completely. Add remaining ingredients, but only half of the flour. Beat with a spoon until smooth.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>