<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>sauce on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</title>
    <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/tags/sauce/</link>
    <description>Recent content in sauce on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:55:27 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bstreete.github.io/public/tags/sauce/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Chipotle Crema</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/chipotle-crema/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:55:27 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/chipotle-crema/</guid>
      <description>Source: The Garden Kitchen
Ingredients  1/2 cup low fat Greek yogurt 1 tablespoon of sauce from chipotle chili peppers in adobo 1 teaspoon lime juice 1/2 teaspoon honey pinch of salt  Directions  Wash hands with soap and warm water. Place all ingredients in a samll bowl and stir until smooth. Taste and add more lime, chipotle, or honey if needed. Serve cold on sandwiches, wraps, or hamburgers. Keeps for up to one week in a sealed container in the refrigerator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doug&#39;s Home Made Salsa</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/dougs-salsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:21:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/dougs-salsa/</guid>
      <description>Source: Doug Silhacek
Ingredients  1/3 bunch of cilantro 1/2 small white onion 2 cloves of garlic 1 can diced fire roasted tomatoes 1 small can of diced green chiles 1/2 tsp of ground oregano 1/2 tsp black pepper Dash of salt Dash of ground cayenne pepper Dash of red pepper flake Juice of 1/2 a lime  Directions  Combine in food processor and chop to desired consistency.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fresno Chile Hot Sauce</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/chile-hot-sauce/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:06:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/chile-hot-sauce/</guid>
      <description>Source: Bon Appetit August 2014
Ingredients  1/2 lb stemmed Fresno chiles (8 - 10) 6 peeled garlic cloves 3 tbsp red wine vinegar Salt, to taste  Directions  Cook chiles and garlic in large saucepan of boiling salted water until chiles turn red, about 2 minutes. Drain. Blend chiles, garlic, and vinegar in a blender until almost smooth. Season with salt and let cool. Can be made a week ahead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Melting Pot Cheddar Cheese Fondue</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/cheddar-fondue/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 08:48:41 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/cheddar-fondue/</guid>
      <description>Source: CopyKat Recipes
Ingredients  6 oz medium sharp cheddar cheese 2 oz Emmenthaler Swiss cheese 4 oz Coors Light 2 tsp chopped garlic 2 tsp Worcestershire sauce 2 Tbsp flour 2 tsp dry mustard powder  Directions  If you are using a fondue pot, turn it onto medium heat Otherwise, use a double boiler to heat the mixture. Combine beer, garlic, mustard powder, and Worcestershire sauce. Shred or cube all cheese, and toss with flour coating the cheese well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buffalo Sauce</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/buffalo-sauce/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 07:11:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/buffalo-sauce/</guid>
      <description>Source: AllRecipes by Chef John
Ingredients  2/3 cup hot pepper sauce (Frank&#39;s RedHot) 1/2 cup cold unsalted butter 1 1/2 tablespoons white vinegar 1/4 teaspoon Worcestershire sauce 1/4 teaspoon cayenne pepper 1/8 teaspoon garlic powder salt to taste  Directions  Combine the hot sauce, butter, vinegar, Worcestershire sauce, cayenne pepper, garlic powder, and salt in a pot and place over medium heat. Bring to a simmer while stirring with a whisk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blackberry Vinegar Caramel</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/blackberry-vinegar-caramel/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 07:11:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/blackberry-vinegar-caramel/</guid>
      <description>Source: Bon Appetit May 2014 Issue
Ingredients  1 c sugar 1/4 c unseasoned rice vinegar 10 oz fresh or frozen blackberries (can use raspberries instead)  Directions  Cook sugar in a medium saucepan over medium heat without stirring, until it begins to turn golden brown around the edges. Stir to incorporate melted sugar and cook, stirring occasionally, until all sugar is melted and caramel turns a deep amber color, 6 to 8 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>