<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>side on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</title>
    <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/tags/side/</link>
    <description>Recent content in side on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 15:31:52 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bstreete.github.io/public/tags/side/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Skillet Cornbread</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/cornbread/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 15:31:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/cornbread/</guid>
      <description>Notes This is a modified version of the original recipe. The chili recipe associated with the cornbread was omitted as I prefer a different chili recipe. The cornbread is quite tasty, but can be cooked independently.
Cornbread goes great with honey and/or butter.
Ingredients  1 cup yellow cornmeal 1 cup all-purpose flour 1/4 cup sugar 4 tsp baking powder 1/2 tsp salt 1 cup milk 1 large egg 1/4 cup cooking oil  Directions Instructions</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kale Salad with Mustard Vinaigrette</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/kale-salad-mustard-vinaigrette/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 14:39:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/kale-salad-mustard-vinaigrette/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients Salad  Medium bunch of kale (best with Lacinto aka &amp;lsquo;Dinosaur&amp;rsquo; kale) 1/2 cup pecan or walnut pieces 1/2 cup dried cherries or cranberries 1/4 cup queso fresco or soft goat cheese 1/2 cup Mustard Vinaigrette  Mustard Vinaigrette Dressing  1/2 small red onion, chopped finely (roughly 1/4 cup) 2 tablespoons rice wine vinegar 1 tablespoon Dijon mustard 1/4 teaspoon salt 1/2 teaspoon pepper 2/3 cup olive oil  Directions Salad  Wash kale and pat dry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweet Potato Pancakes</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/sweet-potato-pancakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 10:00:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/sweet-potato-pancakes/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 pound sweet potatoes (about 2 medium), peeled and coarsely grated 2 scallions, finely chopped 1/3 cup all-purpose flour 2 large eggs, lightly beaten 1 teaspoon salt 1/2 teaspoon black pepper 1/2 teaspoon powdered garlic 1/2 teaspoon ground cumin 2 tablespoons vegetable oil  Directions  Wash hands with soap and warm water. Wash produce well and chop as directed. Stir together all ingredients, except oil, until well mixed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crispy Salt and Vinegar Potatoes</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/salt-vinegar-potatoes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:48:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/salt-vinegar-potatoes/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  2 lb. Baby Yukon Gold potatoes, halved, quartered if large 1 cup plus 2 Tbsp distilled white vinegar 1 Tbsp kosher salt, plus more 2 Tbsp unsalted butter Ground black pepper 2 Tbsp chopped fresh chives Flaky sea salt  Directions  Combine potatoes, 1 cup of vinegar, and 1 Tbsp kosher salt in a medium saucepan; add water to cover by 1&amp;rdquo;. Bring to a boil, reduce heat, and simmer ntil potatoes are tender, 20 - 25 minutes; drain and pat dry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greek Salad with Walnuts </title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/greek-salad-walnuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:29:54 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/greek-salad-walnuts/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients Salad  1 package (10 oz) mixed salad greens 1 c ripe olives 3 plum tomatoes cut into wedges 1 small red onion, thinly sliced 1/2 medium cucumber, peeled, cut into wedges 1/2 c coarsely chopped walnuts 8 oz feta cheese  Dressing  1/2 c Extra Virgin Olive Oil 1/4 c lemon juice 1 clove garlic, minced 1 tsp dried oregano leaves 1/4 tsp pepper 1/4 tsp salt  Directions  Mix salad dressings together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Savory Feta Cheese Log with Toasted Walnuts and Olives</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/feta-cheese-log/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:26:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/feta-cheese-log/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  8 oz feta cheese, crumbled 4 oz cream cheese, softened 1 clove garlic, minced 2 tbsp extra virgin olive oil 1/4 c chopped olives 2 tbsp sliced green onions 1/2 c chopped walnuts  Directions  Mix feta cheese, cream cheese, and oil with electric mixer on medium speed until well blended. Add olives and onions, mix well. Toast walnuts in a large non-stick skillet on medium-high heat 5 minutes, stirring constantly, cool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Herby Corn Salad</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/corn-salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:19:02 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/corn-salad/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1/4 c olive oil 2 tbsp sherry vinegar salt pepper 1 sliced small shallot 1/2 c torn fresh herbs (like dill, mint, and/or - chives) 3 c raw or blanched corn kernels  Directions  Whisk olive oil and vinegar in a large bowl. Season with salt and pepper, add the shallot and herbs. Fold in the corn kernels, and season with salt and pepper.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corn Jalapeno Fritters</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/corn-jalapeno-fritters/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:12:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/corn-jalapeno-fritters/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  2 beaten large eggs 1/4 c all purpose flour 2 tbsp grated parmesan 1/2 tsp kosher salt 2 c fresh corn kernels 1 thinly sliced scallion 1/2 finely chopped jalapeno 2 tbsp vegetable oil Sour cream (optional) Lime wedges (optional)  Directions  Pulse eggs, flour, parmesan, and kosher salt in a food processor to combine. Add corn, scallion, and jalapeno. Pulse 2 to 3 times. Heat vegetable oil in a large nonstick skillet over medium heat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cauliflower Gratinee</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/cauliflower-gratinee/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 07:11:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/cauliflower-gratinee/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  6 tbsp unsalted butter 4 cloves garlic, minced 4 oz thinly sliced prosciutto, cut into thin strips Florets of 1 large head cauliflower, cut into 1/4 in lengthwise- slices 2 tbsp unbleached all purpose flour 1 1/2 c heavy or whipping cream Pinch cayenne pepper Salt and freshly ground black pper, to taste 1 1/2 c grated Swiss cheese 1/2 c chopped fresh parsley  Directions  Preheat oven to 350.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>