<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>slow cooker on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</title>
    <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/tags/slow-cooker/</link>
    <description>Recent content in slow cooker on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 14:51:20 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bstreete.github.io/public/tags/slow-cooker/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Slow Cooker Black Bean Soup</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/black-bean-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 14:51:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/black-bean-soup/</guid>
      <description>Notes Recommend topping with some combination of the following:
 sliced avocado tortilla chips sour cream Tony&#39;s Cajun seasoning  Ingredients  2 cloves garlic 1 medium onion 2 stalks celery 2 medium carrots 1 lb dry uncooked black beans 1 cup salsa 1 Tbsp chili powder 1/2 Tbsp cumin 1 tsp oregano 4 cups vegetable broth 2 cups water  Directions  Mince the garlic, dice the onion and celery, and grate the carrots on a large holed cheese grater.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slow Cooker Pot Roast</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/slow-cook-pot-roast/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 07:11:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/slow-cook-pot-roast/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  One 4-pound beef chuck roast Kosher salt and freshly ground black pepper 1/3 cup all-purpose flour, plus more for coating 3 tablespoons olive oil 4 medium carrots, cut into 2-inch pieces 3 stalks celery, peeled and cut into 2-inch pieces 1 medium onion, cut into 1/2-inch wedges 3 cloves garlic, mashed 3 tablespoons tomato paste 1 cup red wine 3 cups low-sodium beef broth 3 bay leaves 2 sprigs fresh thyme 1/2 teaspoon ground allspice 1/2 cup loosely packed parsley leaves, chopped  Directions  Sprinkle the roast all over with 2 1/2 teaspoons salt and 1 1/2 teaspoons pepper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Authentic Louisiana Red Beans and Rice</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/red-beans-rice/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 17:17:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/red-beans-rice/</guid>
      <description>Note: Can cook in a slow cooker with two cans of prepared kidney beans for four to six hours on low.
Ingredients  1 pound dry kidney beans 1/4 cup olive oil 1 large onion, chopped 1 green bell pepper, chopped 2 tablespoons minced garlic 2 stalks celery, chopped 6 cups water 2 bay leaves 1/2 teaspoon cayenne pepper 1 teaspoon dried thyme 1/4 teaspoon dried sage 1 tablespoon dried parsley 1 teaspoon Cajun seasoning 1 pound andouille sausage, sliced 4 cups water 2 cups long grain white rice  Directions  Rinse beans, and then soak in a large pot of water overnight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Not) Butter Chicken</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/not-butter-chicken/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 15:04:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/not-butter-chicken/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1.25 lbs. 2 lg chicken breasts 3 Tbsp butter 3 cloves garlic 1 med onion 1 inch fresh ginger 1 Tbsp garam masala 1/4 tsp cayenne pepper 1 15 oz. can tomato sauce 1 15 oz. can diced tomatoes 1/2 cup plain yogurt 1 1/2 cups jasmine or basmati rice 2 1/4 cups water  Directions  Trim the fat from the chicken breasts and cut them into small chunks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meaty Beany Chili</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/meaty-beany-chili/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:59:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/meaty-beany-chili/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 tablespoon olive oil 1 yellow onion, diced medium 1 green pepper, seeded, diced medium 6 cloves garlic, minced 2 jalapenos, thinly sliced (seeded, if you want it less - spicy) 3 to 4 tablespoons mild chili powder 1 tablespoon dried mexican oregano 2 teaspoons ground cumin 1 1/2 teaspoons salt Several dashes fresh black pepper 1/8th teaspoon ground cloves 2 cups water (plus extra as needed) - stock is an acceptable substitute 1 cup dried brown lentils 1 28 oz can crushed tomatoes 1 1/2 cups cooked kidney beans, rinsed and drained (15 oz - can) 1 1/2 cups cooked black beans, rinsed and drained (15 oz - can) 1 tablespoon pure maple syrup 2 tablespoons lime juice  Directions  Set your slow cooker to “sear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slow Cooker Chicken Cacciatore </title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/chicken-cacciatore/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:49:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/chicken-cacciatore/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  4 skinless, boneless chicken breasts, trimmed and sliced 1 tbsp dried italian seasoning 1 tsp sweet paprika 1 tsp salt 1/2 tsp black pepper 1/4 tsp crushed red pepper (Try it once before adding more) 1 tbsp olive oil 1 yellow bell pepper, sliced into strips 1 orange bell pepper, sliced into strips 1 onion, diced 3 cloves garlic, minced 1 (28 oz) jar pasta sauce 1 bay leaf 1/2 lb pasta, cooked according to directions fresh parsley (optional) parmesan cheese (optional)  Directions  Toss the chicken pieces with the italian seasoning, paprika, salt, pepper, red pepper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balsamic Roast Beef</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/balsamic-roast-beef/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 07:01:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/balsamic-roast-beef/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  3 – 4 lb chuck roast 1 c beef broth 1/2 c balsamic vinegar 1 tbsp Worcestershire sauce 1 tbsp soy sauce 1 tbsp honey 1/2 tsp red pepper flakes 4 cloves minced garlic  Directions  Place beef in slow cooker. Combine other ingredients in a mixing bowl and pour over the beef. Cook on high 4 hours or low for 6 to 8 hours. (Optional) Reduce the drippings in a saucepan to concentrate the flavor.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>