<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>bread on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</title>
    <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/tags/bread/</link>
    <description>Recent content in bread on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 15:52:27 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bstreete.github.io/public/tags/bread/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Bread Machine Sourdough</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/bread-machine-sourdough/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 15:52:27 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/bread-machine-sourdough/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients for 1.5 lb Loaf  2 teaspoons active dry yeast or instant yeast 1 1/2 teaspoons salt 1 1/2 teaspoons sugar 2 1/2 cups (298g) King Arthur Unbleached All-Purpose Flour or King Arthur Unbleached Bread Flour 2 cups (454g) ripe (fed) sourdough starter 2 tablespoons (25g) vegetable oil 4 to 6 tablespoons (57g to 113g) lukewarm water, enough to make a soft dough  Ingredients for 1 lb Loaf  1 teaspoon active dry yeast or instant yeast 1 teaspoon salt 1 teaspoon sugar 1 2/3 cups (198g) King Arthur Unbleached All-Purpose Flour or King Arthur Unbleached Bread Flour 1 1/3 cups (301g) ripe (fed) sourdough starter 1 tablespoon (13g) vegetable oil 3 to 4 tablespoons (43g to 57g) lukewarm water, enough to make a soft dough  Directions  Place the ingredients into the pan of your machine, in the order suggested by the manufacturer; program for French Bread, or a similar long-rising cycle; and press start.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dill Cottage Cheese Bread</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/dill-cottage-cheese-bread/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 07:52:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/dill-cottage-cheese-bread/</guid>
      <description>Notes  Can omit the dill for a wonderful, simple white bread.  Ingredients  1 package dry yeast 1/4 cup warm water 1 cup creamed cottage cheese 2 tablespoons sugar 1 tablespoon minced onion 1 teaspoon dill seed 1 teaspoon salt 1/4 teaspoon baking soda 1 egg beaten 2 1/4 to 2 1/2 cups flour 1/4 cup shortening  Directions  In a large bowl, dissolve the yeast in warm water.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Country White Bread</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/country-white-bread/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 10:10:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/country-white-bread/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients For 1 Pound Loaf  1 cup water 1 tablespoon sugar 1 1/2 teaspoons salt 2 cups bread flour 1 1/2 teaspoons yeast  For 1 1/2 Pound Loaf  1 1/2 cups water 1 1/2 tablespoons sugar 2 teaspoons salt 3 cups bread flour 2 1/2 teaspoons yeast  Directions Bake according to bread machine instructions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oat &#39;n Chocolate Bars</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/oat-chocolate-bars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 16:07:06 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/oat-chocolate-bars/</guid>
      <description>Notes Can double recipe and use a 13&amp;rdquo; by 9&amp;rdquo; pan. Do not attempt to do more than double or the end result is soggy.
Ingredients  1/2 cup flour 1/2 teaspoon salt 1/2 teaspoon baking powder 1 1/4 cup quick oats 1 6 oz package of chocalate chips 1/2 cup shortening or margarine 1 cup brown sugar 1 teaspoon vanilla 2 eggs  Directions  Mix flour, salt, baking powder, and quick oats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carrot &amp; Banana Bread</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/carrot-banana-bread/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 15:59:34 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/carrot-banana-bread/</guid>
      <description>Notes  Makes 1 9&amp;rdquo; by 5&amp;rdquo; loaf pan. Can double recipe and put in a bundt pan to serve 10. Lis always skips the topping.  Ingredients Bread Ingredients  8 oz flour 1 teaspoon baking soda 1/2 teaspoon salt 5 oz brown sugar 4 oz grated carrots 2 ripe bananas mashed 2 eggs 1/2 cup vegetable oil  Optional Topping Ingredients  2 oz soft margarine or cream cheese 6 oz sugar grated rind and juice of 1 orange 1/2 egg white beaten orange wedges to decorate  Directions  Preheat oven to 350°.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Banana Bread</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/banana-bread/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 15:44:57 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/banana-bread/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1/2 cup butter 1 cup sugar 2 beaten eggs 3 ripe, mashed bananas 2 cups all purpose flour 1 teaspoon salt 1 teaspoon baking soda mixed with 3 tablespoons of cold water 1 teaspoon vanilla 1/2 cup chopped nuts  Directions  Cream butter and sugar until light. Add beaten eggs and mashed bananas. Sift flour and salt together and add to the first mixture. Add baking soda, vanilla, and nuts and mix well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skillet Cornbread</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/cornbread/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 15:31:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/cornbread/</guid>
      <description>Notes This is a modified version of the original recipe. The chili recipe associated with the cornbread was omitted as I prefer a different chili recipe. The cornbread is quite tasty, but can be cooked independently.
Cornbread goes great with honey and/or butter.
Ingredients  1 cup yellow cornmeal 1 cup all-purpose flour 1/4 cup sugar 4 tsp baking powder 1/2 tsp salt 1 cup milk 1 large egg 1/4 cup cooking oil  Directions Instructions</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baked French Toast</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/baked-french-toast/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:56:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/baked-french-toast/</guid>
      <description>Notes Frozen berries work well when baking.
Ingredients  Loaf of French bread 3 eggs 3 tablespoons sugar 1 teaspoon vanilla 2 1/4 cup milk 1/2 cup flour 6 tablespoons brown sugar 1/2 teaspoon cinnamon 1/4 cup butter 1 cup berries  Directions  Cut bread diagonally. Place in baking dish. Beat eggs, sugar, and vanilla together. Stir in milk and pour over bread. Turn slices to coat well. Cover and refrigerate at least two hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wry Braid (Onion Bread)</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/onion-bread/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:45:44 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/onion-bread/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  2 packages active dry yeast 2 cups warm water 1 envelope onion soup mix 1/3 c sugar 2 tbsp molasses 1 tsp salt 1 egg 1/3 c soft shortening 6 to 6 1/2 c flour (not self-rising)  Directions  In mixing bowl, dissolve yeast in warm water. Add soup mix, stir to dissolve completely. Add remaining ingredients, but only half of the flour. Beat with a spoon until smooth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Knead Herb Bread</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/no-knead-herb-bread/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:40:54 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/no-knead-herb-bread/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  3 c all purpose flour 1 tsp salt 1 tbsp sugar 1 (2 1/2 tsp) package active dry yeast 1 1/4 c warm water 2 tbsp shortening or softened butter 3 tsp dried sage 1/2 tsp dried rosemary 1/4 tsp dried thyme 1 tsp melted butter  Directions  Combine 2 cups flour, salt, sugar, and yeast in a large bowl. Stir in the water, shortening, sage, rosemary, and thyme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easy Pizza Dough</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/easy-pizza-dough/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:23:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/easy-pizza-dough/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 c warm water 1 package of yeast 1 tsp salt 2 1/2 c of flour 2 Tbsp olive oil  Directions  Dissolve yeast in warm water Mix in flour, salt, and oil in 20 hard strokes. (Don&#39;t overmix) Let rest 20 minutes. Flour your hands, and divide into two portions. On an oiled and cornmealed pan, pat the dough into an ~ 11 in. circle using your hands.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>