<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>soup on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</title>
    <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/tags/soup/</link>
    <description>Recent content in soup on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 14:52:05 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bstreete.github.io/public/tags/soup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Potato Soup with Bacon and Cheddar</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/potato-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 14:52:05 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/potato-soup/</guid>
      <description>Source: Emeril
Ingredients  4 strips bacon, diced 2 cups chopped yellow onion 1/4 cup minced shallot 1 tablespoon minced garlic 2 1/2 pounds Idaho potatoes, peeled and cut into 1/2-inch dice, reserved in a bowl of cold water 5 cups chicken stock or canned, low-sodium chicken broth 3/4 teaspoon salt 1/4 teaspoon ground white pepper 1/4 teaspoon ground black pepper, plus more for garnish 1/2 cup heavy cream 2 tablespoons chopped green onion tops, plus more for garnish 8 ounces grated sharp Cheddar, for garnish (recommend doubling)  Note: Can use broccoli instead of bacon, and olive oil instead of bacon grease for a lighter soup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roasted Butternut Squash Soup</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/butternut-squash-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 14:49:43 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/butternut-squash-soup/</guid>
      <description>Source: The Garden Kitchen
Ingredients  1 Large (2 to 3 pound) butternut squash 1 tablespoon olive oil salt and pepper to taste 1 onion, roughly chopped 1 tablespoon chopped fresh sage 3 garlic cloves, roasted 4 cups vegetable broth 1/4 cup toasted pumpkin seeds (optional)  Directions  Preheat oven to 400°F. Line or grease a baking sheet. Cut the squash in half lengthwise and remove the seeds. Place on the baking sheet, brush with olive oil, and sprinkle with salt and pepper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pappa Al Pomodoro</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/pappa-al-pomodoro/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:47:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/pappa-al-pomodoro/</guid>
      <description>Source: Bon Appetit August 2014
Ingredients  2 lb tomatoes, cored and quartered 2 garlic cloves, smashed 1/2 tsp fennel seeds 6 tbsp olive oil Kosher salt Black pepper 4 sprigs basil 1/4 loaf country style bread, crust removed torn into 2&amp;rdquo; pieces  Directions  Preheat oven to 450. Toss tomatoes, garlic, fennel, and 3 tbsp olive oil in a large baking dish. Season with salt and pepper. Roast, stirring occasionally, until the tomatoes are browned and the juices thicken, 30 to 35 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>