<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Garden Kitchen on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</title>
    <link>https://bstreete.github.io/author/the-garden-kitchen/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The Garden Kitchen on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 14:49:43 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bstreete.github.io/author/the-garden-kitchen/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Roasted Butternut Squash Soup</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/butternut-squash-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 14:49:43 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/butternut-squash-soup/</guid>
      <description>Source: The Garden Kitchen
Ingredients  1 Large (2 to 3 pound) butternut squash 1 tablespoon olive oil salt and pepper to taste 1 onion, roughly chopped 1 tablespoon chopped fresh sage 3 garlic cloves, roasted 4 cups vegetable broth 1/4 cup toasted pumpkin seeds (optional)  Directions  Preheat oven to 400°F. Line or grease a baking sheet. Cut the squash in half lengthwise and remove the seeds. Place on the baking sheet, brush with olive oil, and sprinkle with salt and pepper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kale Salad with Mustard Vinaigrette</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/kale-salad-mustard-vinaigrette/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 14:39:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/kale-salad-mustard-vinaigrette/</guid>
      <description>Source: The Garden Kitchen
Ingredients Salad  Medium bunch of kale (best with Lacinto aka &amp;lsquo;Dinosaur&amp;rsquo; kale) 1/2 cup pecan or walnut pieces 1/2 cup dried cherries or cranberries 1/4 cup queso fresco or soft goat cheese 1/2 cup Mustard Vinaigrette  Mustard Vinaigrette Dressing  1/2 small red onion, chopped finely (roughly 1/4 cup) 2 tablespoons rice wine vinegar 1 tablespoon Dijon mustard 1/4 teaspoon salt 1/2 teaspoon pepper 2/3 cup olive oil  Directions Salad  Wash kale and pat dry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweet Potato Pancakes</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/sweet-potato-pancakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 10:00:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/sweet-potato-pancakes/</guid>
      <description>Source: The Garden Kitchen
Ingredients  1 pound sweet potatoes (about 2 medium), peeled and coarsely grated 2 scallions, finely chopped 1/3 cup all-purpose flour 2 large eggs, lightly beaten 1 teaspoon salt 1/2 teaspoon black pepper 1/2 teaspoon powdered garlic 1/2 teaspoon ground cumin 2 tablespoons vegetable oil  Directions  Wash hands with soap and warm water. Wash produce well and chop as directed. Stir together all ingredients, except oil, until well mixed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chipotle Crema</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/chipotle-crema/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:55:27 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/recipes/chipotle-crema/</guid>
      <description>Source: The Garden Kitchen
Ingredients  1/2 cup low fat Greek yogurt 1 tablespoon of sauce from chipotle chili peppers in adobo 1 teaspoon lime juice 1/2 teaspoon honey pinch of salt  Directions  Wash hands with soap and warm water. Place all ingredients in a samll bowl and stir until smooth. Taste and add more lime, chipotle, or honey if needed. Serve cold on sandwiches, wraps, or hamburgers. Keeps for up to one week in a sealed container in the refrigerator.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>