<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>favorites on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</title>
    <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/tags/favorites/</link>
    <description>Recent content in favorites on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 16:32:09 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bstreete.github.io/public/tags/favorites/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Skillet Spanakopita</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/skillet-spanakopita/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 16:32:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/skillet-spanakopita/</guid>
      <description>Taken from How to Cook Everything Fast, page 468-469
Ingredients  10 to 12 sheets of phyllo dough 3 tablespoons olive oil 4 scallions two 10-ounce bags of spinach salt and pepper 2 eggs 6 ounces feta cheese (1 1/2 cups crumbled) 1 teaspoon dried dill 1/4 teaspoon nutmeg 4 tablespoons butter  Directions  Remove phyllo from freezer. Heat oven to 350 degrees. Put olive oil in a medium ovenproof skillet over low heat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tricolour Pulao</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/tricolour-pulao/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 09:06:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/tricolour-pulao/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  225g/8oz/1 cup basmati rice, rinsed and soaked for 30 minutes 30 ml/2 tbsp vegetable oil 2.5 ml/ 1/2 tsp cumin seeds 2 dried bay leaves 4 green cardamom pods 4 cloves 1 onion, finely chopped 1 carrot, finely diced 50g/2oz/1/2 cup frozen peas, thawed 50g/2oz/1/2 cup frozen sweetcorn, thawed 25g/1oz/1/4 cup cashew nuts, lightly fried 475ml/16fl oz/2 cups water 1.5ml/1/4 tsp ground cumin  Directions  Heat oil in a wok, karahi, or large pan over medium heat, and fry the cumin seeds for 2 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indonesian Style Satay</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/indonesian-satay/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 08:48:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/indonesian-satay/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients Protein Ingredients  1 1/2 pounds lean boneless beef (sirloin or top round), pork (butt or leg), or chicken 1 clove garlic, minced or pressed 2 tablespoons soy sauce 1 tablespoon salad oil 1 teaspoon ground cumin 1 teaspoon ground coriander  Basting Sauce Ingredients  3 tablespoons lemon juice 2 tablespoons soy sauce 1/4 teaspoon ground cumin 1/4 teaspoon ground coriander  Peanut Sauce Ingredients  1 cup water 2/3 cup creamy or crunchy peanut butter 2 cloves garlic, minced or pressed 2 tablespoons brown sugar 1 1/2 tablespoons lemon juice 1 tablespoon soy sauce 1/4 to 1/2 teaspoon chili paste or crushed red pepper  Directions Protein Directions  Cut meat into 3/4 inch cubes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Picatta</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/chicken-picatta/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 08:07:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/chicken-picatta/</guid>
      <description>Recommend serving over angelhair pasta with a side of roasted asparagus.
Ingredients  chicken breasts flour, seasoned with salt and pepper white wine lemon juice butter 2 tablespoons capers olive oil  Directions  Pound chicken to desired thinness. Dredge in flour. Saute dredged chicken in a half olive oil, half butter mixture until golden. Move chicken to plate. Slowly pour wine into pan to deglaze. Add lemon juice to taste (be generous).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pastalaya</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/pastalaya/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 14:57:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/pastalaya/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 Tbsp vegetable oil 1/2 lb smoked sausage (preferably Andouille) 2 cloves garlic 1 onion 1 bell pepper 2 ribs of celery 15 oz can diced tomatoes 1/2 Tbsp Creole seasoning 1/2 tsp oregano 1/2 tsp smoked paprika 1/4 tsp thyme Freshly cracked pepper 2 cups chicken broth 1 cup water 1 lb penne pasta 2 Tbsp half and half or cream 1/2 bunch fresh parsley 1/2 bunch green onions  Directions  Slice the smoked sausage into thin rounds, then cut any larger pieces in half.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slow Cooker Black Bean Soup</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/black-bean-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 14:51:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/black-bean-soup/</guid>
      <description>Notes Recommend topping with some combination of the following:
 sliced avocado tortilla chips sour cream Tony&amp;rsquo;s Cajun seasoning  Ingredients  2 cloves garlic 1 medium onion 2 stalks celery 2 medium carrots 1 lb dry uncooked black beans 1 cup salsa 1 Tbsp chili powder 1/2 Tbsp cumin 1 tsp oregano 4 cups vegetable broth 2 cups water  Directions  Mince the garlic, dice the onion and celery, and grate the carrots on a large holed cheese grater.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Broccoli Cheddar Casserole</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/broccoli-cheddar-casserole/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 14:45:39 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/broccoli-cheddar-casserole/</guid>
      <description>Notes You can omit the cayenne if sensitive to heat.
Ingredients  1 lb. frozen broccoli florets 8 oz. medium or sharp cheddar, shredded 4 cups cooked rice (white or brown) 1 small yellow onion 2 cloves garlic 3 Tbsp butter 3 Tbsp all-purpose flour 2 cups milk (2% milk fat or higher) 1/2 tsp salt 1/4 tsp smoked paprika 1/8 tsp cayenne pepper Freshly cracked black pepper  Directions  Roughly chop the broccoli florets into smaller, bite-sized pieces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buddha Bowls</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/buddha-bowls/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 07:07:58 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/buddha-bowls/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 large sweet potato, peeled and cut into 1/2-inch cubes 1 large red onion, diced 3 tbsp. extra-virgin olive oil, divided Kosher salt Freshly ground black pepper 1 lb. boneless, skinless chicken breasts 1/2 tsp. garlic powder 1/2 tsp. ground ginger 1 small clove garlic, minced 2 tbsp. creamy peanut butter 1/4 c. Juice of 1 lime 1 tbsp. low-sodium soy sauce 1 tbsp. honey 1 tbsp. toasted sesame oil 4 c.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cross Rib Roast</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/rib-roast/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2019 12:31:07 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/rib-roast/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  2 pounds cross-rib roast 2 tablespoons balsamic vinegar 2 tablespoons minced garlic 2 teaspoons dried thyme 1 teaspoon dried rosemary 1 tablespoon salt 1 teaspoon pepper 1 tablespoon olive oil  Directions  Brush roast with balsamic vinegar. Make a paste with remaining ingredients and apply to meat. Roast meat at 450 for 15 minutes. Reduce heat to 350 and cook for 40 to 60 minutes, or until internal temperature reaches 125.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Authentic Louisiana Red Beans and Rice</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/red-beans-rice/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 17:17:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/red-beans-rice/</guid>
      <description>Note: Can cook in a slow cooker with two cans of prepared kidney beans for four to six hours on low.
Ingredients  1 pound dry kidney beans 1/4 cup olive oil 1 large onion, chopped 1 green bell pepper, chopped 2 tablespoons minced garlic 2 stalks celery, chopped 6 cups water 2 bay leaves 1/2 teaspoon cayenne pepper 1 teaspoon dried thyme 1/4 teaspoon dried sage 1 tablespoon dried parsley 1 teaspoon Cajun seasoning 1 pound andouille sausage, sliced 4 cups water 2 cups long grain white rice  Directions  Rinse beans, and then soak in a large pot of water overnight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homemade Falafel with Tahini Sauce</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/falafel-with-tahini/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 17:14:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/falafel-with-tahini/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients Falafel  2 cups roughly chopped white onion 6 garlic cloves 2 cups cooked chickpeas, drained 1 cup lightly packed parsley leaves 1 cup lightly packed cilantro leaves 1 teaspoon salt 1/4 teaspoon chili powder 2 teaspoons cumin 2 teaspoons baking powder 1/2 cup all-purpose flour Canola oil, for sauteing Pita bread, for serving  Tahini Sauce  1/4 cups plain yogurt (full fat or non-fat) 1/4 cup tahini (sesame paste) Tablespoons fresh lemon juice  Directions  Add the onion and garlic cloves to the bowl of a food processor and pulse just until they are finely minced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Not) Butter Chicken</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/not-butter-chicken/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 15:04:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/not-butter-chicken/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1.25 lbs. 2 lg chicken breasts 3 Tbsp butter 3 cloves garlic 1 med onion 1 inch fresh ginger 1 Tbsp garam masala 1/4 tsp cayenne pepper 1 15 oz. can tomato sauce 1 15 oz. can diced tomatoes 1/2 cup plain yogurt 1 1/2 cups jasmine or basmati rice 2 1/4 cups water  Directions  Trim the fat from the chicken breasts and cut them into small chunks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lentil &amp; Sausage Stew</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/lentil-sausage-stew/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 14:55:13 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/lentil-sausage-stew/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1/2 lb Italian sausage 1 medium onion 3 medium carrots (1/2 lb) 4 stalks celery (1/2 bunch) 2 cloves garlic 2 cups brown lentils 6 cups chicken broth 1/2 tsp cayenne 1 tsp smoked paprika 1 tsp cumin 1 tsp oregano 10 oz frozen spinach  Directions  Brown the sausage in a large pot over medium heat, breaking it up into pieces as it cooks. While the sausage is cooking, prepare your vegetables: wash, peel and slice the carrots, slice the celery, dice the onion, and mince the garlic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple Green-Chile Pie With Cheddar Crust</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/green-chile-apple-pie/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 14:46:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/green-chile-apple-pie/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients Crust  1 ¼ cups all-purpose flour ¼ teaspoon salt ⅓ cup cold unsalted butter, cut into dice ½ cup grated sharp Cheddar cheese 5 tablespoons ice water, more as needed  Filling  5 cups peeled and thickly sliced tart apples, such as Jonagold, Honeycrisp or Granny Smith ½ cup chopped roasted green Hatch chilies, mild or medium hot (see note) 2 tablespoons fresh lemon juice ½ cup granulated sugar ¼ cup light brown sugar ½ teaspoon cinnamon ¼ teaspoon allspice ¼ teaspoon nutmeg, preferably freshly grated ¼ teaspoon salt ¼ cup cornstarch  Topping  ½ cup all-purpose flour ½ cup finely chopped walnuts ¼ cup light brown sugar 4 tablespoons unsalted butter, melted Vanilla ice cream, for serving  Directions  Make the crust: In a food processor or mixer fitted with a paddle attachment, combine flour and salt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meaty Beany Chili</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/meaty-beany-chili/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:59:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/meaty-beany-chili/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 tablespoon olive oil 1 yellow onion, diced medium 1 green pepper, seeded, diced medium 6 cloves garlic, minced 2 jalapenos, thinly sliced (seeded, if you want it less - spicy) 3 to 4 tablespoons mild chili powder 1 tablespoon dried mexican oregano 2 teaspoons ground cumin 1 1/2 teaspoons salt Several dashes fresh black pepper 1/8th teaspoon ground cloves 2 cups water (plus extra as needed) - stock is an acceptable substitute 1 cup dried brown lentils 1 28 oz can crushed tomatoes 1 1/2 cups cooked kidney beans, rinsed and drained (15 oz - can) 1 1/2 cups cooked black beans, rinsed and drained (15 oz - can) 1 tablespoon pure maple syrup 2 tablespoons lime juice  Directions  Set your slow cooker to “sear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baked French Toast</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/baked-french-toast/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:56:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/baked-french-toast/</guid>
      <description>Notes Frozen berries work well when baking.
Ingredients  Loaf of French bread 3 eggs 3 tablespoons sugar 1 teaspoon vanilla 2 1/4 cup milk 1/2 cup flour 6 tablespoons brown sugar 1/2 teaspoon cinnamon 1/4 cup butter 1 cup berries  Directions  Cut bread diagonally. Place in baking dish. Beat eggs, sugar, and vanilla together. Stir in milk and pour over bread. Turn slices to coat well. Cover and refrigerate at least two hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chipotle Crema</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/chipotle-crema/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:55:27 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/chipotle-crema/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1/2 cup low fat Greek yogurt 1 tablespoon of sauce from chipotle chili peppers in adobo 1 teaspoon lime juice 1/2 teaspoon honey pinch of salt  Directions  Wash hands with soap and warm water. Place all ingredients in a small bowl and stir until smooth. Taste and add more lime, chipotle, or honey if needed. Serve cold on sandwiches, wraps, or hamburgers. Keeps for up to one week in a sealed container in the refrigerator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crispy Salt and Vinegar Potatoes</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/salt-vinegar-potatoes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:48:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/salt-vinegar-potatoes/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  2 lb. Baby Yukon Gold potatoes, halved, quartered if large 1 cup plus 2 Tbsp distilled white vinegar 1 Tbsp kosher salt, plus more 2 Tbsp unsalted butter Ground black pepper 2 Tbsp chopped fresh chives Flaky sea salt  Directions  Combine potatoes, 1 cup of vinegar, and 1 Tbsp kosher salt in a medium saucepan; add water to cover by 1&amp;rdquo;. Bring to a boil, reduce heat, and simmer ntil potatoes are tender, 20 - 25 minutes; drain and pat dry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feta Walnut Pasta</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/feta-walnut-pasta/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:26:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/feta-walnut-pasta/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  8 oz rotelle or fusilli pasta 1/2 c chopped walnuts 1 clove garlic, minced 1/2 c sliced green onions 1/3 c extra virgin olive oil 8 oz feta cheese, crumbled 5 oz sliced olives, drained 1/4 c chopped fresh basil  Directions  Cook pasta, and drain. Toast walnuts in a large non-stick skillet on medium high heat 5 minutes, stirring constantly. Remove walnuts from skillet, set aside. Cook and stir garlic and onions in oil on medium heat until tender.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweet Potato Black Bean Chili</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/sweet-potato-black-bean-chili/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 18:05:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/sweet-potato-black-bean-chili/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  2 lbs sweet potatoes, peeled and cubed 1/2 tsp ground dried chipotle pepper 1/2 tsp salt 2 tbsp olive oil 1 onion, diced 4 cloves garlic, minced 1 red bell pepper, diced 1 jalapeno pepper, sliced 2 tbsp ancho chile powder, or to taste 1 tbsp ground cumin 1/4 tsp dried oregano 1 (28 oz) can diced tomatoes 1 c water, or more as needed 1 tbsp cornmeal 1 tsp salt, or to taste 1 tsp white sugar 1 tsp unsweetened cocoa powder 2 (15 oz) cans black beans, washed and drained 1 pinch cayenne pepper 1/2 c sour cream for garnish (optional) 1/4 c chopped fresh cilantro (optional)  Directions  Preheat oven to 400 degrees.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>