<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Food Network on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</title>
    <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/author/food-network/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Food Network on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 08:14:43 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bstreete.github.io/public/author/food-network/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Pappardelle With Corn</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/pappardelle-corn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 08:14:43 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/pappardelle-corn/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  Kosher salt 2 ears corn, shucked 5 tablespoons unsalted butter 3 cups grape tomatoes 2 cloves garlic, minced Freshly ground pepper 1/2 cup white wine 12 ounces pappardelle pasta 1/2 cup low-sodium chicken broth 1 small bunch scallions, thinly sliced 1/2 cup freshly grated parmesan, plus more for topping Torn basil, for topping  Directions  Bring a large pot of salted water to a boil. Add the corn and cook until slightly tender, about 3 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slow Cooker Pork Tacos</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/slow-cooker-pork-tacos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 07:49:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/slow-cooker-pork-tacos/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  3 whole ancho chiles 3 whole pasilla chiles 4 cloves garlic, unpeeled 2 to 3 chipotles in adobo sauce 1/2 medium white onion, roughly chopped 3 tablespoons extra-virgin olive oil 2 tablespoons honey 1 tablespoon cider vinegar Kosher salt 2 teaspoons dried oregano, preferably Mexican 3 3/4 cups low-sodium chicken broth 4 pounds boneless pork shoulder (untrimmed), cut into chunks Freshly ground pepper 2 bay leaves 1 cinnamon stick Corn tortillas, warmed, for serving Assorted taco toppings, for garnish  Directions  Put the ancho and pasilla chiles and the garlic in a bowl; add 2 to 3 tablespoons water.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slow Cooker Pot Roast</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/slow-cook-pot-roast/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 07:11:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/slow-cook-pot-roast/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  One 4-pound beef chuck roast Kosher salt and freshly ground black pepper 1/3 cup all-purpose flour, plus more for coating 3 tablespoons olive oil 4 medium carrots, cut into 2-inch pieces 3 stalks celery, peeled and cut into 2-inch pieces 1 medium onion, cut into 1/2-inch wedges 3 cloves garlic, mashed 3 tablespoons tomato paste 1 cup red wine 3 cups low-sodium beef broth 3 bay leaves 2 sprigs fresh thyme 1/2 teaspoon ground allspice 1/2 cup loosely packed parsley leaves, chopped  Directions  Sprinkle the roast all over with 2 1/2 teaspoons salt and 1 1/2 teaspoons pepper.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>