<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>chili on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</title>
    <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/tags/chili/</link>
    <description>Recent content in chili on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 07:53:27 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bstreete.github.io/public/tags/chili/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Boilermaker Tailgate Chili</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/boilermaker-tailgate-chili/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 07:53:27 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/boilermaker-tailgate-chili/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  2 pounds ground beef chuck 1 pound bulk Italian sausage 3 (15 ounce) cans chili beans, drained 1 (15 ounce) can chili beans in spicy sauce 2 (28 ounce) cans diced tomatoes with juice 1 (6 ounce) can tomato paste 1 large yellow onion, chopped 3 stalks celery, chopped 1 green bell pepper, seeded and chopped 1 red bell pepper, seeded and chopped 2 green chile peppers, seeded and chopped 1 tablespoon bacon bits 4 cubes beef bouillon 1/2 cup beer 1/4 cup chili powder 1 tablespoon Worcestershire sauce 1 tablespoon minced garlic 1 tablespoon dried oregano 2 teaspoons ground cumin 2 teaspoons hot pepper sauce (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skillet Cornbread</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/cornbread/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 15:31:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/cornbread/</guid>
      <description>Notes This is a modified version of the original recipe. The chili recipe associated with the cornbread was omitted as I prefer a different chili recipe. The cornbread is quite tasty, but can be cooked independently.
Cornbread goes great with honey and/or butter.
Ingredients  1 cup yellow cornmeal 1 cup all-purpose flour 1/4 cup sugar 4 tsp baking powder 1/2 tsp salt 1 cup milk 1 large egg 1/4 cup cooking oil  Directions Instructions</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meaty Beany Chili</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/meaty-beany-chili/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:59:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/meaty-beany-chili/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 tablespoon olive oil 1 yellow onion, diced medium 1 green pepper, seeded, diced medium 6 cloves garlic, minced 2 jalapenos, thinly sliced (seeded, if you want it less - spicy) 3 to 4 tablespoons mild chili powder 1 tablespoon dried mexican oregano 2 teaspoons ground cumin 1 1/2 teaspoons salt Several dashes fresh black pepper 1/8th teaspoon ground cloves 2 cups water (plus extra as needed) - stock is an acceptable substitute 1 cup dried brown lentils 1 28 oz can crushed tomatoes 1 1/2 cups cooked kidney beans, rinsed and drained (15 oz - can) 1 1/2 cups cooked black beans, rinsed and drained (15 oz - can) 1 tablespoon pure maple syrup 2 tablespoons lime juice  Directions  Set your slow cooker to “sear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2am Chili</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/2am-chili/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:53:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/2am-chili/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  2 tablespoons flour 1 teaspoon basil 1 tablespoon onion powder 4 teaspoons chili powder 2 teaspoons cumin 1 tablespoon cayenne 1 tablespoon garlic powder 2 teaspoons sugar 3 to 4 cloves of garlic 1 onion 1 bell pepper 1 1/2 pounds of ground beef 1 15oz can of tomato sauce 1 15oz can of diced tomatoes 1 15oz can of corn 1 15oz can of kidney beans 1 can of beer (optional)  Directions  Brown the beef in a skillet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kill City Chili</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/kill-city-chili/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:37:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/kill-city-chili/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  3 tbsp olive oil 2 1/2 lbs ground beef 1/4 c dark chile powder 2 1/2 tbsp curry powder 3 cloves garlic, finely chopped 1 large yellow onion, diced 1 medium green bell pepper, diced 2 16 oz cans kideny beans, drained and rinsed 1 28 oz can crushed tomatoes Kosher salt and ground black pepper, to taste 3 tbsp chopped cilantro, plus more for garnish 1 c grated Monterey Jack cheese for serving Sour cream for serving  Directions  Heat oil in a 6 qt saucepan over medium high heat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweet Potato Black Bean Chili</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/sweet-potato-black-bean-chili/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 18:05:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/sweet-potato-black-bean-chili/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  2 lbs sweet potatoes, peeled and cubed 1/2 tsp ground dried chipotle pepper 1/2 tsp salt 2 tbsp olive oil 1 onion, diced 4 cloves garlic, minced 1 red bell pepper, diced 1 jalapeno pepper, sliced 2 tbsp ancho chile powder, or to taste 1 tbsp ground cumin 1/4 tsp dried oregano 1 (28 oz) can diced tomatoes 1 c water, or more as needed 1 tbsp cornmeal 1 tsp salt, or to taste 1 tsp white sugar 1 tsp unsweetened cocoa powder 2 (15 oz) cans black beans, washed and drained 1 pinch cayenne pepper 1/2 c sour cream for garnish (optional) 1/4 c chopped fresh cilantro (optional)  Directions  Preheat oven to 400 degrees.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>