<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>dessert on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</title>
    <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/tags/dessert/</link>
    <description>Recent content in dessert on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 16:12:23 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bstreete.github.io/public/tags/dessert/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Chocolate Pecan Pie</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/chocolate-pecan-pie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 16:12:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/chocolate-pecan-pie/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 15 oz premade pie crust 3 eggs, slightly beaten 1 cup karo light or dark corn syrup 1/2 cup sugar 1/2 cup semisweet chocolate chips, melted 2 tablespoons margarine, melted 1 teaspoon vanilla 1 1/2 cup pecans  Directions  Prepare pie crust according to package directions. Flute as directed. In medium bowl, stir eggs, corn syrup, sugar, chocolate, margarine, and vanilla until well blended. Stir in pecans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oat &#39;n Chocolate Bars</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/oat-chocolate-bars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 16:07:06 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/oat-chocolate-bars/</guid>
      <description>Notes Can double recipe and use a 13&amp;rdquo; by 9&amp;rdquo; pan. Do not attempt to do more than double or the end result is soggy.
Ingredients  1/2 cup flour 1/2 teaspoon salt 1/2 teaspoon baking powder 1 1/4 cup quick oats 1 6 oz package of chocalate chips 1/2 cup shortening or margarine 1 cup brown sugar 1 teaspoon vanilla 2 eggs  Directions  Mix flour, salt, baking powder, and quick oats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carrot &amp; Banana Bread</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/carrot-banana-bread/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 15:59:34 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/carrot-banana-bread/</guid>
      <description>Notes  Makes 1 9&amp;rdquo; by 5&amp;rdquo; loaf pan. Can double recipe and put in a bundt pan to serve 10. Lis always skips the topping.  Ingredients Bread Ingredients  8 oz flour 1 teaspoon baking soda 1/2 teaspoon salt 5 oz brown sugar 4 oz grated carrots 2 ripe bananas mashed 2 eggs 1/2 cup vegetable oil  Optional Topping Ingredients  2 oz soft margarine or cream cheese 6 oz sugar grated rind and juice of 1 orange 1/2 egg white beaten orange wedges to decorate  Directions  Preheat oven to 350°.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blueberry Rum Pie</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/blueberry-rum-pie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 15:53:46 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/blueberry-rum-pie/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients Crust Ingredients  1 1/4 cup graham cracker crumbs 1/4 cup soft margarine (or butter) 2 tablespoons sugar  Filling Ingredients  12 oz cream cheese 1/2 cup sugar 2 eggs, well beaten 1/4 teaspoon rum extract 2 cup fresh or frozen blueberries  Topping Ingredients  1 cup sour cream 2 tablespoons sugar 2 tablespoons sweet sherry  Directions  Preheat oven to 350°. In bowl, mix crumbs, butter, and sugar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Banana Bread</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/banana-bread/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 15:44:57 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/banana-bread/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1/2 cup butter 1 cup sugar 2 beaten eggs 3 ripe, mashed bananas 2 cups all purpose flour 1 teaspoon salt 1 teaspoon baking soda mixed with 3 tablespoons of cold water 1 teaspoon vanilla 1/2 cup chopped nuts  Directions  Cream butter and sugar until light. Add beaten eggs and mashed bananas. Sift flour and salt together and add to the first mixture. Add baking soda, vanilla, and nuts and mix well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carrot Cake</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/carrot-cake/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 15:20:32 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/carrot-cake/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients Optional Ingredients Raisins and walnuts are an optional (and welcome) addition to the cake mix.
Cake Ingredients  Unsalted butter, for the pan 12 ounces, approximately 2 1/2 cups, all-purpose flour, plus - extra for pan 12 ounces grated carrots, medium grate, approximately 6 medium 1 teaspoon baking powder 1 teaspoon baking soda 1/4 teaspoon ground allspice 1/4 teaspoon ground cinnamon 1/4 teaspoon freshly ground nutmeg 1/2 teaspoon salt 10 ounces sugar, approximately 1 1/3 cups 2 ounces dark brown sugar, approximately 1/4 cup firmly packed 3 large eggs 6 ounces plain yogurt 6 ounces vegetable oil  Frosting Ingredients  8 ounces cream cheese 2 ounces unsalted butter, room temperature 1 teaspoon vanilla extract 9 ounces powdered sugar, sifted, approximately 2 cups  Directions Cake Directions  Preheat oven to 350 degrees F.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Applesauce Cake VI</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/applesauce-cake/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 15:13:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/applesauce-cake/</guid>
      <description>Notes Can substitute green chile applesauce for the regular applesauce for a delicious New Mexican style dessert.
Ingredients  3 cups all-purpose flour 3 teaspoons baking powder 2 teaspoons baking soda 1/2 teaspoon salt 2 teaspoons ground cinnamon 4 eggs 2 cups white sugar 1 1/2 cups vegetable oil 2 cups applesauce 1 teaspoon vanilla extract  Directions  Preheat oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C). Grease and flour a 10 inch tube pan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basically Strawberry Shortcakes</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/strawberry-shortcakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 15:09:39 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/strawberry-shortcakes/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  2 cups all-purpose flour, plus more for surface 1½ tsp. baking powder ¼ tsp. baking soda ½ cup plus 1 tsp. sugar, divided 1½ tsp. kosher salt, plus more 1 lemon ½ cup (1 stick) cold unsalted butter 1 cup sour cream, divided 2 cups heavy cream, divided 1½ lb. strawberries 1 tsp. vanilla extract  Directions  Place a rack in center of oven; preheat to 400°. Line a rimmed baking sheet with parchment paper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple Green-Chile Pie With Cheddar Crust</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/green-chile-apple-pie/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 14:46:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/green-chile-apple-pie/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients Crust  1 ¼ cups all-purpose flour ¼ teaspoon salt ⅓ cup cold unsalted butter, cut into dice ½ cup grated sharp Cheddar cheese 5 tablespoons ice water, more as needed  Filling  5 cups peeled and thickly sliced tart apples, such as Jonagold, Honeycrisp or Granny Smith ½ cup chopped roasted green Hatch chilies, mild or medium hot (see note) 2 tablespoons fresh lemon juice ½ cup granulated sugar ¼ cup light brown sugar ½ teaspoon cinnamon ¼ teaspoon allspice ¼ teaspoon nutmeg, preferably freshly grated ¼ teaspoon salt ¼ cup cornstarch  Topping  ½ cup all-purpose flour ½ cup finely chopped walnuts ¼ cup light brown sugar 4 tablespoons unsalted butter, melted Vanilla ice cream, for serving  Directions  Make the crust: In a food processor or mixer fitted with a paddle attachment, combine flour and salt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Classic Spritz Cookies </title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/spritz-cookies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:51:41 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/spritz-cookies/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  3 1/2 c all purpose flour 1 tsp baking powder 1 1/2 cups softened butter 1 c granulated sugar 1 egg 2 Tbsp milk 1 tsp clear vanilla extract 1/2 tsp no-color almond extract  Directions  Preheat oven to 350. Combine flour and baking powder. In large bowl, beat butter and sugar with electric mixer until light and fluffy. Add egg, milk, vanilla, and almond extract; mix well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheesecake</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/cheesecake/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:04:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/cheesecake/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 graham (or other) crust 2 pkg cream cheese 1/3 c sugar 1 tbls milk 1 tbls vanilla 1 egg  Directions  Mix everything but the crust together. Pour the mix into the crust. Bake in a preheated oven at 350 for 30 minutes. Let cool and enjoy.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blackberry Vinegar Caramel</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/blackberry-vinegar-caramel/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 07:11:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/blackberry-vinegar-caramel/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 c sugar 1/4 c unseasoned rice vinegar 10 oz fresh or frozen blackberries (can use raspberries instead)  Directions  Cook sugar in a medium saucepan over medium heat without stirring, until it begins to turn golden brown around the edges. Stir to incorporate melted sugar and cook, stirring occasionally, until all sugar is melted and caramel turns a deep amber color, 6 to 8 minutes. Remove pan from heat and carefullly add vinegar to caramel (mixture will bubble vigorously), then add berries.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>