<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>dessert on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</title>
    <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/tags/dessert/</link>
    <description>Recent content in dessert on Brayden&#39;s Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:51:41 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bstreete.github.io/public/tags/dessert/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Classic Spritz Cookies </title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/spritz-cookies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:51:41 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/spritz-cookies/</guid>
      <description>Source: Wilton Home 
Ingredients  3 1/2 c all purpose flour 1 tsp baking powder 1 1/2 cups softened butter 1 c granulated sugar 1 egg 2 Tbsp milk 1 tsp clear vanilla extract 1/2 tsp no-color almond extract  Directions  Preheat oven to 350. Combine flour and baking powder. In large bowl, beat butter and sugar with electric mixer until light and fluffy. Add egg, milk, vanilla, and almond extract; mix well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheesecake</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/cheesecake/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:04:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/cheesecake/</guid>
      <description>Source: Unknown
Ingredients  1 graham (or other) crust 2 pkg cream cheese 1/3 c sugar 1 tbls milk 1 tbls vanilla 1 egg  Directions  Mix everything but the crust together. Pour the mix into the crust. Bake in a preheated oven at 350 for 30 minutes. Let cool and enjoy.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blackberry Vinegar Caramel</title>
      <link>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/blackberry-vinegar-caramel/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 07:11:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bstreete.github.io/public/recipes/blackberry-vinegar-caramel/</guid>
      <description>Source: Bon Appetit May 2014 Issue
Ingredients  1 c sugar 1/4 c unseasoned rice vinegar 10 oz fresh or frozen blackberries (can use raspberries instead)  Directions  Cook sugar in a medium saucepan over medium heat without stirring, until it begins to turn golden brown around the edges. Stir to incorporate melted sugar and cook, stirring occasionally, until all sugar is melted and caramel turns a deep amber color, 6 to 8 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>